<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<bugrepository name="WhisperSystems_Signal-Android">
	<bug id="5272">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Selecting multiple attachments to send crashes the app </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description If I want to send someone more than one image at once (I know that's not implemented (#4629), but selecting them is possible with e.g. Amaze File Manager or any other file managing app I guess), Signal crashes. As far as I investigated there is no difference between a Signal contact and an SMS contact. Tested it with images and audio files. Steps to reproduce Press the attachment button and select image Choose your favorite file managing app for the action (I used Amaze File Manager) Select multiple images and click select Crash Device info Model: Fairphone 1U Android version: 4.2.2 Signal version: 3.11.1 Edit: Added debug log: https://gist.github.com/anonymous/e886d1a7dbececee762e</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/MediaUtil.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/31970c4644552e1e3effd4c97f343dda204531eb</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="6009">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Archive title is not updated after language change </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description The title of the archived conversations activity is not translated to the language that is set at the moment. Instead it shows up in the language that was set during your first visit to this activity. Steps to reproduce Open Signal Enter archive Go back to conversation list Change language in Settings -> Appearance to any other language Go back to conversation list Enter archive Actual result: The title has the language which was set during your first visit to the archive. Expected result: The title has the language which is set at the moment. Screenshots Device info Device: Fairphone 2 Android version: 5.1.1 Signal version: 3.25.4 👍 2</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationListArchiveActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/e5fcc465c9cc1b67413f29a3196a248e9b545558</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3398">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>blocked contact list does not update after change of block status </summary>
			<description>block A Settings > Privacy > Blocked contacts notice A is in the list tap A Unblock go back notice that A is still in the blocked list tap A notice that A is not actually blocked</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/RecipientPreferenceDatabase.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/c05555c290730541b02bb0f8600a150a166c5649</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5919">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Constantly crashing when trying to answer unknown group recovery request </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description @moxie0 I was testing #5876. The device that is trying to answer the request for unknown group details is constantly crashing on startup. Steps to reproduce Devices A and B in a group A running current beta 3.24.0, B still on 3.23.0 Re-install on device B sent group message from device A to B B receives message in unknown group update device B to Signal 3.24.0 sent another message from A to B Actual result: Device A is crashing on startup since then Expected result: Device A should answer B's request and not crash Device info Device A: Nexus 5 Android version: Stock Android 5.1.1 Signal version: see above Link to debug log I can only send a Google Feedback report after the crash. I get this in Android Studio: W/JobConsumer: java.lang.NullPointerException: Attempt to get length of null array</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/PushGroupUpdateJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/d9ff5b00b7e5b778acf196b29182b5784377718f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1558">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>MMS doesn't work unless you enter override settings </summary>
			<description>Well it's as the title says, I only realised this after searching Google. That's a terrible thing. FYI, I had to enter http://mmsc.t-mobile.co.uk:8002 149.254.201.135 8080</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/ApnDefaults.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/12e92b9cdf96070d6a626d298fd98b5a01da5ca0</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1362">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>[bug] Forwarding media messages only forwards text </summary>
			<description>Sharing pictures from the gallery or anywhere else works great in 2.0.7., but whenever I want to forward a message with an image, only the text gets transferred into the new message. Observed behaviour: Forwarding messages with pictures only forwards the text. Expected behaviour: Forwarding messages with pictures forwards the whole message. @McLoo identified the problem in ConversationFragment.java (#316 (comment)):   private void handleForwardMessage(MessageRecord message) {</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/PartAuthority.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/AttachmentManager.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/SmsSendtoActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationFragment.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ShareActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/NewConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/02c37e815cecb41a2378a8134130afd1f51bb5d1</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2333">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Difficult to select some messages </summary>
			<description>After I upgraded from 2.3.3 to 2.4.0 I have difficulties selecting some messages. Not all messages - it seems to be just those messages where TextSecure recognises a phonenumber in the message text. When I long-press such a message and release my finger from the screen the selection disappears. To select such a message I have to long press, don't release my finger, press another message in the thread so I select 2 messages and then short-press the last one so it leaves the selection. Update: I tested this on 2 devices, one no-name cheap Android 4.2.2 which does not have this problem. A Sony XPeria Z1 Compact with 4.4.4 does have this problem.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable/conversation_item_background.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationAdapter.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable/conversation_item_background_dark.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/BindableConversationItem.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_fragment.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_item_received.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/themes.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_item_sent.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/99d3374d35b5027850fdc31c8a2620fb5f83fbf7</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5461">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Group Images are still not getting resized. </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description Sending a large Image (f.i. 13MPixel, ~6MB .jpg) to a Group doesn't resize the Image to a lower dimension and filesize. When you send the same Image to a single Contact in contrary, it -does- resize the image. This leads to a large amount of traffic use on both ends. Group images should ideally be handled the same way as single contact images. In a perfect version, the user should be asked for whether it should resize the image or not. This issue has actually been found and fixed 1 year ago here BUT it is still happening in the latest Version of Signal: #2913 Steps to reproduce create a group, add one or more contacts. send a large image (13 MPixel / ~ 6 MB) to this group. Actual result: The Image is not getting resized and Signal sends a whole 6 MB image to the group. The group receives (and has to download) a full 6 MB Image. Expected result: You actually send a resized image (1280 * xxxx, ~200 KB) to that group. The group receives and downloads just a 200 KB Image. Device info Device: LG G3 Android version: 6.0.1 Signal version: 3.15.2 👍 1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/PushGroupSendJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/792d4a5939b4a55b75c08f3aa310edb88c35f78b</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3548">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Dark theme groups use light theme's color </summary>
			<description>The group color in 2.21.0 dark theme is the same blue as in light theme: The dark theme should have it's own color in groups as it has with private chats. (N.B.: The colors in the above screen shots are not accurate. I forgot to turn off my screen shading/color temperature altering app before taking those shots. But the issue is still valid :)</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/color/MaterialColor.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/ad8a290ca5e4d48a394a42c80fa6b7470ec07770</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2871">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Unable to run instrumentation tests due to proguard </summary>
			<description>Running ./gradlew proguardDebugTest now fails (probably an issue with the refactor). The log is huge so I've put it on pastebin: http://pastebin.com/rkQ0BxUZ</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>proguard-appcompat-v7.pro</file>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
			<file>proguard-testing.pro</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a413346610848651db7184b9b3025295bbdf210e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5878">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>'Verify safety numbers' missing </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description I cannot verify contacts anymore. Clicking the contact's name, there is no item 'Verify safety numbers'. On my synced Signal Desktop the option 'Verify identity' exists. Steps to reproduce Do a fresh install of Signal choose a contact that you know is using Signal Actual result: the menu item 'Verify safety numbers' is missing Expected result: the menu item 'Verify safety numbers' is not missing Screenshots Device info Device: Samsung Galaxy Note 3 Neo Android version: 4.4.2 Signal version: 3.22.2 Link to debug log https://gist.github.com/anonymous/56d73f7a56a54ccd82586a73920bc881 👍 1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/RecipientPreferenceActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/bd819d7d10b87399f95fa062ef326ea68a04b65e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5930">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Deleted group reappears when contact safety number changes </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description A deleted group shows up again when a group member's security number changes, so without exchanging messages in that group. The group then appears to be in an inactive state, i.e. sending messages is not possible. Steps to reproduce Create a group, group members A and B Delete group on device A (you can even leave the group first) Re-install Signal on device B (safety number changes) Send a message from A to B Confirm safety number change notification on device A Actual result: All deleted groups that contain B reappear on device A. The only content is a safety number change notification, see 848a256. Sending messages is not possible. Expected result: The groups should not reappear. I was surprised to see that group information where still available at all. Device info Android version: stock Android 5.1.1 Signal version: 3.24.1 👍 2</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/IdentityUpdateJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/01bc2ebde4aace915fda2b60a88b7e4f7a0eb580</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2508">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Crash Browser -- MMS Exception </summary>
			<description>java.lang.RuntimeException: Value length > LENGTH_QUOTE!</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/MmsReceiveJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/e70298e6244dbfd6e1f7fe16a809136f25051dab</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="321">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Feature request for TextSecure: Unread count on icon </summary>
			<description>When I'm pushing TextSecure onto friends and family to spread adoption of encrypted communications, the showstopper is the lack of an unread messages count on the icon, like all other messaging apps have today. When I send text messages to my mother, she will never read them, because when she turns her phone on, TextSecure won't show on her home screen as "1 unread message" with a little red circled "1" on the TextSecure icon. Drawing from UX from all other messaging apps today, the lack of such a number will instead indicate "nothing unread". I understand such an indicator is a privacy leak, but it's also an adoption showstopper to take TextSecure beyond the hardcore carers for cryptography, and by extension, even the ability for people like ourselves to communicate securely with friends and family (since they won't use TextSecure). Cheers, Rick</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/1d0c9536fc5bb4954501b763f81e0c5a7d1995e0</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1954">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Search doesnt find groups </summary>
			<description>Groups that are visible in the regular conversations view are not found when searching for their names. Its probably the same issue that has been pointed out here http://support.whispersystems.org/customer/portal/questions/8473126-can-t-see-send-to-groups I am quite sure that this was not the case back in July. If I recall correctly then it was also possible to find the groups in the contacts screen (the one that pops up when hitting +). Device info: HTC Desire HD, Cyanogenmod 7.3, TextSecure 2.1.8</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/GroupDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/contacts/ContactAccessor.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/loaders/ConversationListLoader.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/33d466a5cc37bab12b3718d45cf308cf5231e150</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3199">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>emoji keyboard consumes all space on rotate from portrait to landscape </summary>
			<description>tested on 4c89b24 on my N5 have device in portrait open a conversation click on the message composition edit text open the emoji keyboard rotate device to landscape emoji errewhere</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/values/dimens.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiDrawer.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationPopupActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/KeyboardAwareLinearLayout.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/bc787f20e33b2f1023f0798abfcbd3665c247e1c</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2287">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>notification unread message when locking textsecure </summary>
			<description>Evertytime I lock TextSecure I get a notification about an unread message from a certain contact (always the same contact), but it is wrong as I already have read all messages.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/DatabaseUpgradeActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/PushDatabase.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/7b3bd2fbf76df306a6cc44837ae1de4e17b1fce9</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3600">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>NPE: switching to SMS when message length is >144 (i.e. SMS message counter toggled) </summary>
			<description>A crash mentioned by @merkste in #3571 Type a string that has at least 145 characters¹ on the compose field An example string (158 chars): "Bless the Maker and His water," Kynes murmured. "Bless the coming and going of Him. May His passage cleanse the world. May He keep the world for His people."</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/SendButton.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/TransportOptionsPopup.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/transport_selection.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/35159ac4567a4e22c15e5b958a65981f43c916fb</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5517">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Message shown in status bar with enabled option "Display in notifications: Name only" </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description The option "Name only" in the notification settings under "Display in notifications" is enabled. If you only receive messages from one person this works as intended. But if you have an unread message from one person and receive a new message from another person, the text of the second message is shown in the status bar of the phone. Steps to reproduce Change the notification settings under Notifications > Display in notifications to Name only Receive message from one person (do not read the message!) Receive message from another person Actual result: The message from the second person should appear as "New message" in the status bar of the phone Expected result: The actual message appears Device info Device: Fairphone 1U Android version: 4.2.2 Signal version: 3.16.0 Link to debug log https://gist.github.com/anonymous/b314d9bf5fb0184386839b471e801f1e</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/AbstractNotificationBuilder.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/SingleRecipientNotificationBuilder.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a370f086c0dcbd93b4c89abc410fb9f4708e2945</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5098">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Shadow above the message text box when texts are covered </summary>
			<description>This is how Signal currently looks when texts are covered: This is what Google messenger does when texts are covered: As you can see, a shadow appears on the bottom of the message area on Google messenger, and not on Signal. This bottom shadow serves two purposes: to visually communicate the presence of later messages and to provide consistency with the shadow on the action bar. It would be great if this could be added to Signal.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_fragment.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable/compose_divider_background.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/colors.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationFragment.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/0a72f6b32e160f415cfc93bc04cb06811e01d339</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3562">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>messaged received while in muted thread not marked as read </summary>
			<description>start a new thread with A send some messages back and forth mute A receive message from A while in thread with A back out to conversation list notice that conversation with A is shown as unread</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/72b9c37ec891c0db20e4e5aff2dfaa4218afaad4</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5661">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Bug in new selection of notification messages (save button visible) </summary>
			<description>Hi, build 3.18.0 has introduced the ability to select (and delete) notification messages. For group update messages there is a bug. If you select one the save button becomes visible. (Further on it can be clicked. The same procedure like for media messages will be initiated. However I don't know if really something is saved.) Solution: Hide save button for all kinds of notification messages. Please note that only the notification messages of self initiated group updates are affected by this bug. Notification messages of group updates from other group members are not affected. Found in build 3.18.1. 👍 1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationFragment.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/29548f401925aa018f96d652fad565aa567dff76</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3210">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>PartDatabase unit tests failing </summary>
			<description>a bunch of PartDatabase unit tests are now failing because of dc903e4</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/PartDatabase.java</file>
			<file>test/androidTest/java/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/PartDatabaseTest.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/200fc0c5990fe39c291bad2bbc254c4d5af236bb</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3576">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Conversation list visible when opening direct capture </summary>
			<description>On my HTC One S CM 12.1 with d6d881b the conversation list is visible in the place of the camera preview until the camera preview has loaded when I open direct capture or switch from/to 2nd camera or when the orientation changes or when coming back from screen lock with camera preview still open (not when toggling from half to full screen camera) Hard to screen-shoot this... it's like the convo itself only fills half (or nothing on full screen camera) the screen letting the previous activity sneak through (popup-like).</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/camera/SurfacePreviewStrategy.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/camera/CameraView.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/camera/PreviewStrategy.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/camera/QuickAttachmentDrawer.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/camera/TexturePreviewStrategy.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/5eaaadad2650f984b232b90d8bb5ed945775960e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5304">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Hardcoded string in compose subhint for SIM card </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description While looking into #5294, I noticed that the subhint in ComposeText.java has a hardcoded string:     setHint(transport.getComposeHint(), transport.getSimName().isPresent() ? "From " + transport.getSimName().get() : null);</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ComposeText.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/ba960a82e217a4ce31bc8e7118cf6700c07d9a2f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2494">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>new conversation FAB inaccessible </summary>
			<description>Running the latest TextSecure on an LG Optimus F3Q, I am no longer able to focus the button to compose a new message using the keyboard on the phone. I seem to have no trouble focusing any other elements on the screen, I just can't find this button. I was able to focus the button in the previous version, but I can no longer find it with my arrow keys as of today. I was able to find it by exploring the screen with my finger using both Talkback and Spiel screen readers, but in both cases, the button has no label associated with it, and is now presented to me as simply "button." In order to make best use of this app using my screen reader, the button needs to have a content description associated with it that would allow me to know what the button does. If possible, it should also be able to be focused using a hardware keyboard, whether built in or external.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/023195dd4bf7e36685faafa65c88346425c5acaa</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3563">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Direct audio capture </summary>
			<description>Push-to-talk style. spawned from #520</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_mic_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_mic_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_mic_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_mic_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_mic_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_mic_white_48dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_mic_white_48dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_mic_white_48dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_keyboard_arrow_left_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_mic_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_mic_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/themes.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_keyboard_arrow_left_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_mic_white_48dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_keyboard_arrow_left_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_mic_white_48dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_mic_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_keyboard_arrow_left_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_input_panel.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_keyboard_arrow_left_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_mic_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_mic_white_24dp.png</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/bfe4ad6c34481f40328f0dcbf288ee1bec11eb02</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5674">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Crashes when interacting in app </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description Signal crashes upon interacting with threads or trying to start new conversation. I also cannot view contacts who are not using Signal. The crash will give the "Unfortunately, Signal has stopped," message and exit signal entirely or revert to the main screen with all threads. Had the same issue during beta testing last week. Logged the problem and then uninstalled the beta version. Cleared cache, uninstalled, reinstalled, same problems. Turned on airplane mode, deleted threads, same problem. Messages are being retrieved and presented as notifications through Signal. Changed to phone's messenger as default SMS app in the meantime. Steps to reproduce Open app Touch a conversation or Begin new conversation Select a contact or Click reply on notification Actual result: Immediately, the error message "Unfortunately, Signal has stopped." appears and exits to the home screen of my phone. Expected result: Ability to look at the thread and type and send messages. Device info Device: HTC One M7 Android version: 5.0.2 Signal version: 3.18.2 Link to debug log https://gist.github.com/98d1c821855df39a648ab4b7e107af93 https://gist.github.com/097fe9ba87240354e5108db0dcac35fe 👍 1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/SmsCharacterCalculator.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/893f106189198676d8afe82bab711a382eb75fcb</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5264">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Text does not wrap when "Enter is send" is enabled </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Steps to reproduce Enable "Enter key sends" in Settings > Advanced Type a long message Text does not wrap From a UX perspective, these two things have nothing to do with each other, text could still wrap even if the input field does not allow "multiline" text, otherwise it becomes quite difficult to send long messages and the user has to break it into smaller ones, which might be annoying. Signal version: 3.11 This is not a duplicate of #4219.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ComposeText.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/794e2cb87241445a6fbb8c357e9c343f038b8b60</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2251">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Enter key does not send </summary>
			<description>Hitting enter simply makes a carriage return and does not send a text. This is despite the "Enter key sends" setting being checked. I'm using version 14.0.9 on Android 5.0.1. Thanks.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_ime_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_ime_light.png</file>
			<file>res/xml/preferences_advanced.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_ime_light.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_light.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_ime_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_mood_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_keyboard_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_keyboard_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_ime_light.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_mood_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_keyboard_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_light.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_keyboard_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_light.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_ime_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_mood_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_keyboard_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_mood_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_mood_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_keyboard_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/themes.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_keyboard_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_keyboard_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_mood_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_mood_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_mood_grey600_24dp.png</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/2f20bb89f3b64701d047fa3af2aa8b6e0ecfdc34</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3629">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>"Camera unavailable" when pressing near emoji/keyboard switcher </summary>
			<description>Easiest way to do this is to add a couple of lines in the message with the enter key and press the space above, but it works all around the icon.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/camera/QuickAttachmentDrawer.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/camera/QuickCamera.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/8c63211aafb721bf72e152ffba41f499fc16a776</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="483">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>quick compose quick reply </summary>
			<description>Any plans on implementing quick compose and quick reply?</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/anim/slide_to_top.xml</file>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>res/anim/slide_from_top.xml</file>
			<file>res/menu/conversation_popup.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_launch_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_reply_white_36dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_launch_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_reply_white_36dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_reply_white_36dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_reply_white_36dp.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/values/themes.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_reply_white_36dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_launch_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_launch_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_launch_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationListActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationPopupActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/2016fa315b07a2c88f577e632abf65325bd57a58</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3413">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>TextSecure crashes, when message with Picture is forwarded to other person </summary>
			<description>Hi Im using the beta and TS seems to crash when I try to forward a message with an attached Image I wrote to A to person B. Im on Paranoid Android 5 alpha 2 on Nexus 5.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ShareActivity.java</file>
			<file>test/androidTestEspresso/java/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivityTest.java</file>
			<file>test/androidTestEspresso/java/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivityActions.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/d98cb7b53f4fc3ed3278a3345662409c6268ca0f</commit_url>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/d935be7b0ae69f156d59ca1cf7754c7cedc80b44</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5710">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>SMS only, non-Signal Android contact showing up on Signal Desktop after changing its color </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description Not sure if this problem is on Signal Android's end or on Signal Desktop's. One of my SMS (non-Signal) contacts just got synched with Signal Desktop after changing its color on Signal Android, i. e. the contact is (was) listed on Signal Desktop's contact list - not the conversation. After exiting Signal Desktop and starting it again, that contact magically disappeared again. Edit: I've been able to reproduce this a second time and updated this issue with new debug logs for Signal Android and Signal Desktop. All logs are now taken directly after the issue happened. Potentially related issue: WhisperSystems/Signal-Desktop#903 Steps to reproduce Change color of a non-Signal contact Start Signal Desktop Actual result: Contact shows up on Signal Desktop Expected result: Contact shouldn't show up on Signal Desktop Device info Device: Google Nexus 5 Android version: 6.01 Signal version: 3.19.1 Debug logs: Signal Android directly after changing contact color Signal Desktop directly after contact appeared and is still present Signal Desktop after contact disappeared again</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/RecipientPreferenceActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/MultiDeviceContactUpdateJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/7d1c5a0d40c28785cfd16e09783ed870245e0412</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2686">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Message Details v2.7.0b1 </summary>
			<description>There's no scrolling in Message Details. A long SMS does fill the screen, isn't fully displayed, and the details aren't shown. Regards C</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/MessageDetailsActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/message_details_activity.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/message_recipient_list_item.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/message_details_header.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/dbc28746c0d816e74b2efb074374b1b9f689f589</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3567">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>crash: rotate direct capture **a lot** then tap take photo </summary>
			<description>built from 98b99ef tested on my GB device. debug log: https://gist.github.com/rhodey/1ec213242a0e172642b3 relevant section seems to be: E/AndroidRuntime( 1193): FATAL EXCEPTION: main</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/camera/CameraView.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/camera/QuickCamera.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/d6d881b0cac20ecb5915cf094386aa44662e4ec6</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="520">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Feature: Direct Photo/Video/Audio attachments while staying in app (API calls to camera, sound recorder, video camera) instead of multistep separate apps </summary>
			<description>I love the app... I want to replace it full time from Textra, BUT there is a big draw back, why don't you allow for direct photos, video and sounds to be taken. So you don't have to use two apps to get the file to send. Example: My wife takes a photo of something she wants my opinion on buying, (in textra or native) presses add, camera comes up, takes photo and sends Example: Same situation, but with Text Secure you have to take the photo first and save image, then goto app and add via the menu of "where" the documents are to attach and send So, as you can imagine carrying on a conversation and needing to send several photos during that conversation it would be a bit frustrating and very time consuming using Text Secure. Native, Textra and about all others I have used use API's and directly use the photo/audio to send.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_photo_camera_light.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_photo_camera_dark.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/AnimatingToggle.java</file>
			<file>res/values/themes.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_photo_camera_dark.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_photo_camera_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_photo_camera_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_photo_camera_light.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_photo_camera_light.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_photo_camera_light.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_photo_camera_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_photo_camera_light.png</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/fe4e2fcadba812b8e6cd7db53c3a006f4b67b521</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="247">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>MasterSecretUtil salt size of 8 bytes below NIST recommended minimum of 16 bytes </summary>
			<description>The generateSalt() method in MasterSecretUtil uses 8 bytes (64 bits) while NIST recommends a minimum of 16 bytes (128 bits). https://github.com/WhisperSystems/TextSecure/blob/master/src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/crypto/MasterSecretUtil.java#L235 NIST documentation "Recommendation for Password-Based Key Derivation Part 1: Storage Applications" - http://csrc.nist.gov/publications/nistpubs/800-132/nist-sp800-132.pdf NIST documentation excerpt from page 10, "5.1 The Salt (S) All or a portion of the salt shall be generated using an approved Random Bit Generator (e.g., see [5]). The length of the randomly-generated portion of the salt shall be at least 128 bits." Can this be adjusted to at least 128 bits by changing new byte[8] to new byte[16]?</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/crypto/MasterSecretUtil.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/12d217991cde0378fbb9bd3f42f0615c3c4d2112</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3566">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Doesn't handle group updates in sync messages </summary>
			<description>Per WhisperSystems/Signal-Desktop#274, group updates aren't getting processed for synchronized sent messages.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/PushDecryptJob.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/groups/GroupMessageProcessor.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/OutgoingGroupMediaMessage.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/GroupCreateActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/5fd9874ab6433f91b2863af116c722f5003899e6</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2877">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Bad multi-recipient notification behavior </summary>
			<description>Tapping on a TextSecure notification with multiple senders now opens something that says it's a group chat with 0 members, rather than opening to the ConversationList. I assume this is a regression caused by the RoutingActivity change. I don't know what happens if you try to respond in that group thread, but it can't be good. We should probably try to get a 2.10.1 out asap.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/34fa05cccca97b8d545c8fbe4d828fbf92cf96cb</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="723">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Group chat: Can't send message or leave group after being added a second time </summary>
			<description>Person A creates new group, invites persons B and C and sends message. B leaves group after sending a message and deletes group thread. A adds B again to group. B now gets new group messages, but can't leave again or send any more messages to group. Happened to me on a Galaxy S4 with Android 4.3. I can delete the group thread, but it will appear again as soon as a new message is posted to the group.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/service/GroupReceiver.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/023d776e961045b1822f10d475725b93b3e6066d</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5922">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Crash with UntrustedIdentityException after connecting to Signal Desktop </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description After attempting to pair with Signal Desktop, the Android app crashed while syncing, and now crashes immediately on launch every time, before any complete Activity is displayed (the screen is blank white at the time of crash). It seems similar to #5183, but the first exception in that case (related to the database) does not occur here. No contacts or messages are successfully synced with Desktop. It does not seem obviously related to #5744 or #5426. Steps to reproduce Connect with Desktop app Start syncing between mobile and desktop Actual result: Mobile app crashes during initial sync, and upon any subsequent launch, including when airplane mode is on Expected result: App should open normally Screenshots impossible to take Device info Device: Samsung Galaxy S3 (US AT&T) Android version: 6.0.1 (Cyanogenmod 13) Signal version: 3.23.0 SMS/MMS enabled Debug log via adb 12-03 21:00:58.949   641  1130 I ActivityManager: START u0 {act=android.intent.action.MAIN cat=[android.intent.category.LAUNCHER] flg=0x10200000 cmp=org.thoughtcrime.securesms/.RoutingActivity bnds=[159,1125][293,1280] (has extras)} from uid 10022 on display 0</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/PushDecryptJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/cb23e3a930c1e8f9a00847b988ac4f51ac8b4cc2</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5908">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>labling the unlabled buttons in Signal for Android </summary>
			<description>Hi. I am Pradip Sikdar, a visually challenged android intermediate user. I have started using Signal Private Messanger for Android recently and most of the part, I am quite happy with it. As you know, we use screen reader technology to use our android or IOS devices. So, if there is a menu or button which is not properly tagged or labled, the screen reader doesn't recognize it. For example, let's say there is a play button. Visually there is a sign or graphics which represents that, it is a play button. But if the button is not properly tagged or labled as "Play" button, our screen reader only says "Button Unlabled". So, we cannot recognize what the button is. So, I am here by requesting to the developer of this nice application, to lable all the buttons of this application. For example, when I am clicking on the "toggle attachment" button, I am getting some additional buttons which are not labled. So, I cannot recognize them. Thanks in advance from all the blind community. Pradip 👍 4</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/attachment_type_selector.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/73bf75f65f5efe98663cfc99f117aac477d90f56</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="641">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>It is not possible to set a group avatar </summary>
			<description>Hello, thanks for your great work. On my CM11 phone it is not possible to set a group avatar. Clicking on the empty group avatar wil open the "image selecting form", but whatever i choose, the group avatar stays empty after selection. Bedt regards, Deccoy</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/BitmapUtil.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/GroupCreateActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a183f8d3879897b5f3af074dafbd11d9be017870</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2691">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>ClassCastException for MMS notification records </summary>
			<description>v2.7.0-b1 https://gist.github.com/18eb6203060d8d58a07a</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationItem.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/71eeb7ca83f12f77baeff3d51091ab849477cd2e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1171">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>sms characters remaining don't account for encoding </summary>
			<description>When composing a new message, the number of required SMSes are calculated based on the type of characters (Cyrillic or Latin) used in the first message of the thread rather than on the characters used for composition. 1 SMS = 60 Cyrillic or 160 Latin characters.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/SmsCharacterCalculator.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/TransportOption.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/PushCharacterCalculator.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/MmsCharacterCalculator.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/CharacterCalculator.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/e4fccbe26e0ad69f1d13e69fbd294d82a2bc3d0a</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1819">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Request - UI : Sliding pannel & option. </summary>
			<description>Hello, I believe that there is a non-sense in the UI with a sliding panel on the left and a "regular" menu. In my sense they should be only one, 2 way to access the "option" is confusing. One thing could be that the sliding menu and the option button could trigger the slide. Regards,</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/arrays.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/themes.xml</file>
			<file>res/menu/text_secure_normal.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_list_activity.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/navigation_drawer_item.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/020d61dd6e324bd578881cb95648ed3f06cd853e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2684">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Dates are displayed in system locale regardless of language setting </summary>
			<description>Currently all the dates and times are diplayed regarding the android system locale using DateUtils.formatDateTime. Sometimes its even mixed because the plurals hours_ago and minutes_ago are translated. My system language is set to german but I'm using TextSecure in english: It would be more consistent if the dates are formatted regarding the textsecure language setting I guess.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/DateUtils.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/MessageDetailsActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationAdapter.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationItem.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationListItem.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationListAdapter.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationListActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/PassphraseRequiredActionBarActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationFragment.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationListFragment.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/d8521637bb2a545d02d2b7a32127a4f01b6d0317</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1004">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Image flickers during send </summary>
			<description>I just wrote a message to a group and lost my wifi connection. After I hit 'send', an image shown in a message above started flickering rapidly. The flickering only stopped after the message was eventually delivered. Could it be the case that the image is repeatedly redrawn with each attempt to send the message?</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationItem.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/AudioSlide.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ThumbnailView.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/BubbleContainer.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/Util.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/Slide.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/TextSlide.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ForegroundImageView.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/082985276f4abd066f9c4f07052ab5c82f576c34</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="4168">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>possible to add dupe contact to group </summary>
			<description>No description provided.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/GroupCreateActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/76b0183e0fb6177b5c040e87aa6a0853ed76f9c6</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="4641">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Unlinking device: endless Wheels of Confusion </summary>
			<description>Unlink a device The Wheel of Confusion spins till heat death This is just a visual problem. I.e. the device gets actually unlinked. Tested on 3.5.0 (though the wheels have been spinning since summer... was just too afraid to report it before :) Nexus 4, stock 5.1.1 Huawei U8800, 4.0.4 Edit: Also tested when there are more than one device linked. Same issue.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/AsyncLoader.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/DeviceListFragment.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/loaders/DeviceListLoader.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/d00441e20d4818200eb1e012488daf0e9ebe6b1b</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5749">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Dark theme: 'Tap to scan' on new safety number verification view unreadable </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description verify_display_fragment__tap_to_scan is barely readable on the dark theme (on an actual device it's worse than on the screenshot posted below). Steps to reproduce Switch to dark theme Open a conversation Open new safety number verification view Actual result: Font color far too light for a white background Expected result: Font color should be a lot darker Screenshots Device info Device: LG Nexus 5X Android version: 7.0.0 Signal version: 3.20.2 👍 4</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/verify_display_fragment.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/ff2cb6935d6347cffe1cff90f18cb7a69a067991</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2768">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>PassphraseChangeActivity not using AsyncTask for MasterSecretUtil.changeMasterSecretPassphrase() </summary>
			<description>PassphraseChangeActivity is calling MasterSecretUtil.changeMasterSecretPassphrase() on the UI thread. https://github.com/WhisperSystems/TextSecure/blob/master/src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/PassphraseChangeActivity.java#L100</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/PassphraseChangeActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/58664fcddb4933c435d47d1996d80c66224bda4d</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="4245">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Low quality contact photo during call </summary>
			<description>Calling screen doesn't show the full resolution contact photo on Signal 3.0.3</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/redphone_call_card.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_contact_picture_large.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_contact_picture_large.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_contact_picture_large.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/redphone/ui/CallCard.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/contacts/avatars/GeneratedContactPhoto.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_contact_picture_large.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_contact_picture_large.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/contacts/avatars/ContactPhotoFactory.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/1abf39685a22a5c9a401d0111ca3ff914ab6d2d2</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1329">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Actionbar locale for single/multi contact selection not changing until restart </summary>
			<description>If you switch the selected language the title in the action bar is not translate until restart. It keeps the language that was set on startup. started in spanish, and switched to french Would have fixed that, but @mcginty is heavily working on that region so I issued this first.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/PushContactSelectionActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/VerifyIdentityActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ShareActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/NewConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/GroupCreateActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ReviewIdentitiesActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/454673cd0c11273b9043343ff5b908df7f2b51bf</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="222">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Feature: Blocking </summary>
			<description>Blocking by user-specified phone number, via something like an email filter rule where the messages from the number are deleted upon receipt and no notification is given.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/recipient_preference_activity.xml</file>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/blocked_contacts_fragment.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/menu/conversation_unmuted.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_list_item_view.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_title_view.xml</file>
			<file>res/menu/conversation_muted.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/arrays.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/blocked_contact_list_item.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/40af2a81dbe43ec89fcfea88d33b52814074d90f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3271">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>CrashBrowser: EmojiPageFragment NPE </summary>
			<description>Happening in production on the 2.16.2 staged rollout: java.lang.RuntimeException: Unable to start activity ComponentInfo{org.thoughtcrime.securesms/org.thoughtcrime.securesms.ConversationActivity}: java.lang.NullPointerException</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/emoji_drawer_stub.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>...s/components/emoji/EmojiPageFragment.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiDrawer.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiEditText.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/ce610e0262ec01ff91a3fb1b73fe932c9ee0dde0</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5760">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Crash when changing the conversation settings of an SMS conversation </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description Signal crashes when changing any of the Conversation settings of an SMS conversation. This doesn't happen with encrypted conversations. Steps to reproduce tap on an SMS conversation open the "Conversation settings" Change the state of "Mute conversation" (this also works with the other settings, but this is the quick way to reproduce it) Actual result: Signal crashes and reopens when I click on Ok. Expected result: The settings should change, Signal should not crash. Screenshots It's hard to take one, because the screen goes black after the crash. Device info Device: Moto G 2 Android version: 6.0.1 Signal version: 3.20.2 Link to debug log log.zip</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/RecipientPreferenceActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/21258f244c7a7cfbe79046df740972c60d9753be</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="168">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>TextSecure stops receiving messages after being closed from 'recent apps' list </summary>
			<description>Open TS & enter passphrase Go to homescreen or another app Press/hold 'home' softkey/on-screen button Remove TS from the list by swiping it left/right Messages now go to native Android client rather than TS Device: Samsung Galaxy S2 (Hercules/SGH-T989) OS: Android 4.2.2</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/service/KeyCachingService.java</file>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/DummyActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/b5fe378bc92aa87e33a2909ee183247d65f773bf</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3661">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>emoji drawer incorrectly sized after swiftkey relayout </summary>
			<description>Play version 2.22.1 Z1 compact 5.0.2 without words, literally 🙊</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/SoftKeyboardUtil.java</file>
			<file>res/values/dimens.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/Util.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/camera/QuickAttachmentDrawer.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiDrawer.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/KeyboardAwareLinearLayout.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/7c32e5b1fb9e8cf9d34e9395ae499cad6a4b8899</commit_url>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/39c0fc0e5a33c578965e6e8e7d42527279d3e5b7</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="6043">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>getActiveNotifications() throws an NPE on Android 6.0.1 (mostly Motorola ROMs) </summary>
			<description>Edited by @2-4601: This issue is about a crash when opening notifications. Most of the affected devices are Motorola's running Android 6.0.1. E AndroidRuntime: FATAL EXCEPTION: AsyncTask #2</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/360c2b2a5090b0be87dd8a03245e5f198305c590</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="342">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Export Plaintext Backup sometimes creates invalid XML </summary>
			<description>For some messages, the 'body' attribute in the xml file doesn't get closed. This causes "Error importing backup!" when trying to import. Example of bad XML: <sms protocol="0" address="5558675309" date="1378522000531" type="1" subject="null" body="Hello world  toa="null" sc_toa="null" service_center="null" read="1" status="0" locked="0" /></description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/XmlBackup.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/d429f9113bf475937c3d885ad77b87f25f81fada</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1937">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>MMS sending (and receiving) fails if on WiFi and APN is set to IPv6 </summary>
			<description>Hello, I am having trouble sending and receiving MMS on my T-Mobile USA Samsung galaxy S4 (Android 4.4.4) while connected to WiFi. I am using TextSecure 2.1.8. It looks like the problems have something to do with the switch from IPv4 (on WiFi) to IPv6 on the cellular network. If I manually disable WiFi and send a MMS through TextSecure on the IPv6 only APN, the MMS is correctly sent and received. If I manually switch the APN to IPv4 only, then TextSecure correctly sends and receives MMS while connected to WiFi (by transitioning to the cellular network to send the MMS). However, if I use the default APN of the phone (IPv6 only) and I am connected to the IPv4 only WiFi, sending fails. The logs show that TextSecure attempts to connect to the cellular, but then times out connecting to the MMSC (2607:7700:0:5::ab8:4b81) because of Network unreachable.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/ApnDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/MmsDownloadJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/427c9a6b21ddc2adac93bc8d28644ad353177026</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1935">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>MMS MSISDN/Line1 headers missing </summary>
			<description>I'm new to using TextSecure and I'm sorry if this is a dupe but I couldn't find a similar issue. I just made TextSecure my default messaging app and when trying to download an MMS image, I receive "Error connecting to MMS provider..." I used the following manual MMS settings, as found in my phone's system menu (##3282#): MMSC URL: http://mmsc.vmobl.com:8088 MMS Proxy Host: 68.28.31.2 MMS Proxy Port: 80 A debug log can be found at http://hastebin.com/idofelenev I think the log cut off the attempt to download MMS with the proxy, but in previous attempts it looked similar. Virgin Mobile US, Android 4.4.2, TextSecure 2.1.8</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/MmsSendJob.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/IncomingMmsConnection.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/MmsConnection.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/OutgoingMmsConnection.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/TelephonyUtil.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/b998c5f86ce7b15ef192eb4106948e03e5e71467</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="354">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Adding per-contact notification preferences </summary>
			<description>I'm working to add functionality to TextSecure to allow customization of notifications (ringtone, vibrate pattern, led color) on a per-contact basis. I've got two questions: Is this a feature that you'd be interested in including in mainline TextSecure, and If so, would it be better to let android store the per-contact preferences in the usual preferences location or would it be better to add them to the IdentityDatabase? Thanks!</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/recipient_preference_activity.xml</file>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/blocked_contacts_fragment.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/menu/conversation_unmuted.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_list_item_view.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_title_view.xml</file>
			<file>res/menu/conversation_muted.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/arrays.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/blocked_contact_list_item.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/40af2a81dbe43ec89fcfea88d33b52814074d90f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="6069">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Unread notification badges do not work on Huawei EMUI </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description I've installed Signal on a Honor 8 (made by Huawei) with EMUI 4.1 (Android 6.0). I've noticed that Signal receives notifications on new messages and they are also listed in the notification area, but the unread notifications badge on the app icon on the home screen is not shown. In Signal support articles there is mentioned, that badge icons are supported for some launchers, see https://support.whispersystems.org/hc/en-us/articles/215766077-How-can-I-see-my-unread-badge-count-What-launcher-should-I-use- So far I could not find out if this is a Signal or EMUI problem, but Threema and Conversations show the notification badges. Device info Device: Honor 8 Android version: 6.0 Signal version: 3.26.2</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/86df150374b29222796c1d7060e2252aae6e4fdb</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3449">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Time/date not translated in image view </summary>
			<description>2.19.0 Edit: see third comment for a proper bug report.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/MediaPreviewActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/3136cadf59958a0c2061bbba55ff159473a62303</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5992">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Add Iran to censored countries list </summary>
			<description>Here is the log that I can't connect to textsecure-service.whispersystems.org https://gist.github.com/anonymous/fea6d946aea279e0a748ef4094d575af Thank you so much.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/push/SignalServiceNetworkAccess.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/bb1ab2e9295707de35737bf4d66a5244027ad120</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3307">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Message disappears on send when sharing photo </summary>
			<description>I first noticed this after the recent update to the Photos app. When sharing from within that app, a toast notification says "Sharing to TextSecure..." and the message composition process continues as expected. When sent, the message disappears. This bug does not happen when the sharing process is started from within TextSecure through either the paperclip icon or the "Add attachment" menu option. Nexus 5, Android 5.1.1 (LMY48B), T-Mobile US</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ShareActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/cb3cf7789ff8d5b90ca69c73764b92c82e41b9d9</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="4905">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Disable notification sounds from phone while using desktop client </summary>
			<description>Mobile phone plays notification sound for every message received when using desktop client, which is annoying in e.g. office environment. There should be an option to disable sounds while using desktop client. Possible implementation: Start a timer in the android app whenever a desktop client is used (e.g. message is read, sent or so) for, say 1 minute (or configurable) and during that timer, don't play the notification sound. If a message arrives while timer is active, then keep a flag. If the timer is reset (by desktop interaction), clear the flag, otherwise play the notification sound after the timer expires. This way, the phone is mute while the user is having a desktop conversation, but there will be a notification in case when a message arrives from a remote party shortly after closing the desktop client or so. 👍 10</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/PushDecryptJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/3787551878473c703a21210aa24d39080ad57ad4</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2408">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>"Error sending message" if group member uninstalls TextSecure </summary>
			<description>In a group chat, a member removed TextSecure or unregistered from the service. Since then, all messages yield to "Error sending message" although the other remaining group members receive the messages successfully. I also did not find a way to remove that member from the group. In the log I get these exceptions: W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): org.whispersystems.textsecure.api.push.exceptions.UnregisteredUserException: org.whispersystems.textsecure.api.push.exceptions.NotFoundException: Not found W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.whispersystems.textsecure.internal.push.PushServiceSocket.sendMessage(PushServiceSocket.java:148) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.whispersystems.textsecure.api.TextSecureMessageSender.sendMessage(TextSecureMessageSender.java:177) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.whispersystems.textsecure.api.TextSecureMessageSender.sendMessage(TextSecureMessageSender.java:156) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.whispersystems.textsecure.api.TextSecureMessageSender.sendMessage(TextSecureMessageSender.java:99) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.thoughtcrime.securesms.jobs.PushGroupSendJob.deliver(PushGroupSendJob.java:138) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.thoughtcrime.securesms.jobs.PushGroupSendJob.onSend(PushGroupSendJob.java:74) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.thoughtcrime.securesms.jobs.SendJob.onRun(SendJob.java:38) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.thoughtcrime.securesms.jobs.MasterSecretJob.onRun(MasterSecretJob.java:18) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.whispersystems.jobqueue.JobConsumer.runJob(JobConsumer.java:72) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.whispersystems.jobqueue.JobConsumer.run(JobConsumer.java:46) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): Caused by: org.whispersystems.textsecure.api.push.exceptions.NotFoundException: Not found W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.whispersystems.textsecure.internal.push.PushServiceSocket.makeBaseRequest(PushServiceSocket.java:447) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.whispersystems.textsecure.internal.push.PushServiceSocket.makeRequest(PushServiceSocket.java:410) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): at org.whispersystems.textsecure.internal.push.PushServiceSocket.sendMessage(PushServiceSocket.java:146) W/TextSecureMessageSender( 3082): ... 9 more</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/PushGroupSendJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/021942fd4358ac88eb1642933731b8a9fa39622f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3266">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>emoji not properly ellipsized in single-line textviews </summary>
			<description>If I send a long-ish message to someone, then go back to the conversation list, that message runs off the right side of the screen. This might be ok since it shows as much of the message as my screen will tolerate.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiFilter.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/37fbd769b754322a646c0f6a39c052ad768a4273</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="786">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>multiple message selection within a thread </summary>
			<description>PLEASE add the ability to select or deselect multiple messages from within a thread to delete. Example: I have a thread which has the address of the contact contained in it. I can't delete the thread, because then I lose the address. If there are 300 other messages in that thread, I'd have to go through them one at a time to delete them and keep the 1 message I care about. GoSMSPro has this capability and is the ONLY reason I currently use it. I would prefer to go with TextSecure, but this one feature will keep me from doing so.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationAdapter.java</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationFragment.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/ed556fbd3a5e2c9a4ce841c1a8f12b82529e6784</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="4290">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>leaving conversation doesn't stop audio playback </summary>
			<description>play audio hit back keep jamming to those nice beats</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/audio/AudioSlidePlayer.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/d70f0f1216065790f463cc73a791a71de1a5ff1c</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="4333">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>allow direct sharing to contacts via 6.0 ChooserTargetService </summary>
			<description>https://developer.android.com/reference/android/service/chooser/ChooserTargetService.html 👍 10</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ShareActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/ThreadDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/service/DirectShareService.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a125fcb8fae88119919716f0c295239ce3cfa1c5</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3676">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Some views are still using previous emoji set </summary>
			<description>(Since the last issue was kidnapped I made this.) Per-recipient preferences are using the old emoji set. Screenshot from group preferences:</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/recipient_filter_item.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/recipient_preference_activity.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/contact_selection_list_item.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/13578bb8c0897735b6e7562654ecbd893982d141</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3110">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Glide Crash </summary>
			<description>java.lang.IllegalArgumentException: You cannot start a load for a destroyed activity</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ThumbnailView.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/8332342d7564ecd40d9f26eee751373519637292</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="4131">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>MMS doesn't send on CDMA carriers that require NAI header </summary>
			<description>I posted this elsewhere but I suppose I better open it as a new issue. I can send MSS / picture messages fine using the default android messaging application. I cannot send them using TextSecure. I'm using Google Project Fi as my provider (which uses Sprint & T-Mobile). Unable to send MMS messages. Debug log below. Device : motorola Nexus 6 (shamu)</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/CompatMmsConnection.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/dd986dbc4bbf8cefc6fc8dba6ad4b715cc160c73</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2583">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Adding an invite should not replace a draft message </summary>
			<description>It should be appended to the draft instead, otherwise it's a dataloss.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/76d0f45b9bbe622664323fb48f3bcb4035c7cea0</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="4874">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Links won't open in new tabs </summary>
			<description>Since version 3.7.2, it is impossible to open multiple links from a conversation in separate browser tabs, as every link will be opened in the same tab and so, overwrite the previously opened link. I am using Firefox for Android. It does not seem to be a Firefox bug, as with other apps the browser behaves as expected (it is opening a new tab for every link)</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/3aa024e55372dfa72d8eafac507dd089420eaa63</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2578">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Add sms: uri schema handler </summary>
			<description>If I click on an sms hyperlink in a web browser (such as <a href='sms:555-555-5555'>Call me, maybe?</a> textsecure does not come up as an option. Since you can only send sms from your default sms app, this makes it so these links essentially are unusable when textsecure is your default sms app. Note: smsto: does not work either.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>androidTest/java/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/Rfc5724UriTest.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/SmsSendtoActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/Rfc5724Uri.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/8f002bd68d719772a031dbcb2febb161d5a60223</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5798">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Add possibility to share safety numbers </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Feature Request Besides #5795 (copyable safety numbers) it would be nice to have a share button in the action bar of VerifyIdentityActivity. This would offer a faster work flow for sharing the safety number compared to "copy & paste". 👍 2</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/menu/verify_identity.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/VerifyIdentityActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_share_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_share_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_share_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_share_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_share_white_24dp.png</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/92aeafc26172fbbce036cdf99b82f8313acb204b</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2632">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Notification can show incorrect message receipt time </summary>
			<description>If I have a notification for two (or more) messages from different senders, the notification correctly displays the time of the most recent message. However, if I read this second message without reading the first one, the notification time is updated to the time that I read the second message, rather than the receipt time of the first message.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/NotificationItem.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/bcd9aa84d678d3932c9078f67ef66ad1912122d9</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="580">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Non-preferred phone number first in search results </summary>
			<description>Phone: HTC One V Android: 4.0.3 HTC Sense: 4.0 Textsecure: Latest (Play Store) When searching for a recipient during composing, TextSecure sometimes will not list the preferred number first for the recipient. For example, these screenshots show that although the Mobile number for this recipient is preferred[1], the search results show the Home number first[2].</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/contacts/ContactAccessor.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/468eb3382c3dc47864d067e9eabe51f44daed5c4</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="4732">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Black or wrong image thumbnails </summary>
			<description>#4612 and #4599 Spin-off Just opened a convo with last message = outgoing text+ image message Preview thumb in convo list showed up fine In-convo the (attached from attachment drawer) image thumb is black Reproduced two times now, on 2 tries opening the said convo https://gist.github.com/9d319c95ba0757c7cebb</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/RecentPhotoViewRail.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/RoundedCorners.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/recent_photo_view_item.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/4ad989cc38f6cbe2963524ae3ace455c2ee951b4</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5404">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>buggy comparison in apkdiff </summary>
			<description>hw42@ipsumj.de found that https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/blob/master/apkdiff/apkdiff.py#L64 should be 'or' not 'and'. with 'and' an empty file is equal to everything. (hw42 doesnt have a github account, so I commited this on his behalf.)</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>apkdiff/apkdiff.py</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/b94c72ea7fd3c60be235ce9b7b6a0b3fbedfa15c</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5376">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Regression: Displayed identity key format </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description Hexadecimal numbers used for identity keys are displayed in the format "(byte)0xaa" for each byte since the latest beta. Steps to reproduce Contact preferences Verify identity Actual result: Hex identity key bytes are displayed as "(byte)0xaa" Expected result: Hex identity key bytes should be displayed in the format "aa" Screenshots None Device info Device: Google Nexus 5 Android version: 6.0.1 Signal version: 3.15.0 Link to debug log None 👍 1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/VerifyIdentityActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ViewIdentityActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/2f64b84838f56818775eba401c26be5908140f7b</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1448">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Crash when receiving MMS </summary>
			<description>This just started in the past couple of days, every time an MMS comes in, TextSecure crashes. My setup is a bit strange since I'm using t-mobile's network with a phone originally designed for AT&T. Recipients of my MMS messages get the "adaptation" error, but this crash when I receive one is new to me. Here's the debug log that I ran just after the crash/app reboot: http://hastebin.com/xitukakiqa</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/MmsDatabase.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/242dbef54e12b7294a03728185f2c666b75846bb</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1460">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>[Bug ?] Key changed events do not generate a notification </summary>
			<description>I encountered this with a friend of mine who reflashed his phone and subsequently reregistered. I had an ongoing chat (using his old key) with him and noticed today that he had sent me a message yesterday and I had to accept the new key. But I didn't get notified about the new message in the notification bar I would expect Textsecure to generate notifications for all events including the key changed event, since this may lead to unnoticed messages, depending on usage pattern of course. If this behaviour is intentional, it would be great to know the rationale behind this. Anyways I want to thank you for your amazing work! Steps to reproduce: User A and User B both register with Textsecure Both Users exchange a couple of messages User B reregisters with Textsecure changing his key User B send User A a Message No notification is shown on User A's device Expected behaviour: User A should be notified of the incoming message with the new key</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/service/PushReceiver.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/8713a85beb9d45e6a8ad217a274459aad564309e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1312">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>App exit transition animation inconsistent </summary>
			<description>The transition animation when the app exists is inconsistent depending on which view you are on. Steps: Open the app (opens to message/text view list) Press home button to exit App exits with zoom out transition animation Again open app and click on any message to open one Press home button to exit App exits with slide to right transition animation (jarring to eyes) Device: Moto G Kit Kat 4.4.2</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/7b3f2c169aeb9e2c6cb756d5afdaf2dfe4095843</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2828">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>CrashBrowser: MMS NPE </summary>
			<description>Lollipop device. java.lang.NullPointerException: Attempt to invoke virtual method 'ws.com.google.android.mms.pdu.PduHeaders ws.com.google.android.mms.pdu.RetrieveConf.getPduHeaders()' on a null object reference</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/IncomingMmsConnection.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/IncomingLegacyMmsConnection.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/IncomingLollipopMmsConnection.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/MmsDownloadJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/491440094b1f253da573a4fa2df75877a6ce5a32</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2800">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>ConversationItem manipulating view in wrong thread </summary>
			<description>If there is ever an error while resolving a conversation item thumbnail then ConversationItem.ThumbnailListener will get a callback to onFailure() which will in turn trigger an uncaught android.view.ViewRoot$CalledFromWrongThreadException exception. https://github.com/WhisperSystems/TextSecure/blob/master/src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationItem.java#L615 call should be moved into handler.post(...)</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationItem.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/857135aab15fa079743391ea43a2ce835d34ea8b</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3303">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Height of Emoji drawer does not match height of system keyboard </summary>
			<description>Hello, using TextSecure 2.16.3 on an LG G2 running latest stock ROM (Android 5.0.2 Lollipop), the height of the Emoji drawer does not match the height of the system keyboard. The Emoji drawer is higher than the system keyboard (tested with Google Keyboard from Play Store). Could you please fix that and make the height of the Emoji drawer equal to the height of the system keyboard? Regards</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/KeyboardAwareLinearLayout.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/0f7f458ce0a8a1ab2d7dc33aabe8425b3afb7f20</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5969">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Image "stickers and scribbles" OOM error, preventable? </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description I was testing "Support for stickers and scribbles" (1b44bdc) on a phone that has (only) 768MB of RAM. The picture to be edited was a 3000 * 4000 pixel (w * h) ~1.9MB jpg. Tapping confirm after minimal editing resulted in a OOM error. I got back to the conversation screen and conversation list by tapping the Android back button. Entering the conversation again from the conversation list then let me sent unsecured SMS only, which is a bad experience. Fortunately "force stop" Signal solves the issue. I wonder if the process would succeed if pictures were scaled before editing? Sending the same picture without prior editing works as expected. Device info Device: HTC Sensation XE Android version: CyanogenMod 12.1 - Android 5.1.1 Signal version: 3.25.0 Link to debug log Alloc concurrent mark sweep GC freed 3(96B) AllocSpace objects, 0(0B) LOS objects, 9% free, 39MB/43MB, paused 4.333ms total 72.143ms</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/scribbles/widget/ScribbleView.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/899f3af5e4a7e2b42d06068583ea0d561b3a1f4a</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5216">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Signal crashes on call screen </summary>
			<description>Signal sometimes crashes when making a call or when receiving incoming calls. Happened a few times just now, but I haven't seen this before, so I assume it is a regression in 3.10.0 or 3.11.0. Maybe #4971? This is all I have so far: E/AndroidRuntime: FATAL EXCEPTION: main</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/ContactPhotoUriLoader.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/redphone/ui/CallCard.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/contacts/avatars/ContactPhotoFactory.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/f1cec5a2ca06581e7f9e0d237b50d7974e6e1fc5</commit_url>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/efdb57e76b8ff6016ee179e8e2b8c7a3c6e7dbaf</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3115">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Update the default led notification color to match the current UI </summary>
			<description>This is such a minor issue that it feels almost a sin reporting this but sometimes details are important. Currently the default led notification color is green. However the only green left in TextSecure are the message bubbles when using unencrypted SMS. Otherwise TextSecure is all about blue now (icon, UI, push messages). Therefore the default led color should follow suit.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/TextSecurePreferences.java</file>
			<file>res/xml/preferences_notifications.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/d0f26f3e971625d23245c79a0126d477717211fa</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1516">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Can't send SMS to numbers with MS Outlook phone number format </summary>
			<description>I'm trying out TextSecure for the first time and wanted to send SMS to friends, who's contacts are stored in my exchange account. The numbers were entered in MS Outlook and are stored in this (year long default) format: +xx (xxx) xxxxxxx</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/SmsSendJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/50c432aaf0b7deb8d8f4f890ff0a8542de5faf9f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1264">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Pending picture </summary>
			<description>Today I received a message (group, push) containing a picture. Presumable my phone lost the internet connection during transfer. Now I am stuck with a message that displays the text alongside the downloading animation instead of the picture. This did not change even after I have a stable connection for a couple of hours. I necessary, I can provide the error log.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>...xtsecure/src/main/java/org/whispersystems/textsecure/internal/push/PushServiceSocket.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a9637baddf22bed58c6dba18ee39ffc543a0751e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3473">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>can't install debug build type on GB </summary>
			<description>adb kill-server adb start-server ./gradlew clean assembleDebug adb install build/outputs/apk/textsecure-debug.apk 5747 KB/s (9441819 bytes in 1.604s)</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ApplicationContext.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/b8039af90574bc9d39d15586712f43fbcced57a3</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3329">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>crash on tap group member from members view </summary>
			<description>tested on 5fe7c68 create a group tap the group members icon tap a contact other than yourself notice the contact info slides up all pretty (lollipop only?) press the back button crash bug debug log D/AndroidRuntime(20393): Shutting down VM</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/recipient_filter_item.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationItem.java</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/message_details_header.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/12255ed453058d1100d068815018d556c8ab224f</commit_url>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/82d7300fc0cfb0303c19a574b0e22f7003f8e9f3</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5980">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>AvatarDownloadJob NPE when trying to open Signal </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description Someone in a group tried to update the group avatar but apparently, something went wrong. Signal Desktop now shows a black avatar in the conversation list and the default avatar in the top bar, while Signal-Android crashes with a NPE in AvatarDownloadJob unless I go into airplane mode. Device info Android version: 4.2.2 Signal version: 3.25.2 Link to debug log E/AndroidRuntime( 3089): FATAL EXCEPTION: JobConsumer-0</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/AvatarDownloadJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/f3f2f29b2396c76a8cffb5d937ec511c7e6091ef</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2751">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Zero character passphrases? </summary>
			<description>Textsecure 2.7.1 Samsung SGH-T399 Android 4.2.2 When setting up a passphrase, textsecure accepts a passphrase that is zero characters long. From a usability standpoint and to avoid confusion, it seems like we should require passphrases to be at least one character long. What do people think?</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/PassphraseChangeActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/6ec9ee89a738b300d97ae32a1d1900dc2654e9a1</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="597">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Display sent time instead of received time </summary>
			<description>It would be nice if there is an option in the settings to display the sent time (as displayed in the "message details") instead of the received time next to the messages.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationItem.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/7ceaf59bccbbf2bddba80dc17d4c9fdb01a3d95f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="555">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Not working in dual sim phone </summary>
			<description>My friend has a dual sim Lava iris 405 and i have samsung galaxy s3. we both have installed the TextSecure when i start secure session, it sends Key exchange message and its received in my friends. After that it says Received and processed key exchange message but he is unable to send me any message, it says error sending. i know its giving problem because its a dual sim phone, text secure app is not able to send sms from particular sim and giving this error. Is dual sim phone supported by textSecure?</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/transport_selection_list_item.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_item_received.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_item_sent.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/6da86e482da9a4451bb81875c39af1658c24e473</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="757">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>different notification settings for group chats </summary>
			<description>It would be very nice to be able to change the notification settings for goups independently from other (personal) chats, as group chats might have a lower priority for the user.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/recipient_preference_activity.xml</file>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/blocked_contacts_fragment.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/menu/conversation_unmuted.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_list_item_view.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_volume_off_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_block_grey600_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_title_view.xml</file>
			<file>res/menu/conversation_muted.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/arrays.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_volume_off_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_block_white_18dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/blocked_contact_list_item.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/40af2a81dbe43ec89fcfea88d33b52814074d90f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3328">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>crash bug on group create </summary>
			<description>tested on 5fe7c68, steps I use to reproduce: create new group type 'qqq' as the group title tap the "add member" EditText start typing 'lol myself' crash debug log</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/recipient_filter_item.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/message_details_header.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/12255ed453058d1100d068815018d556c8ab224f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2793">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Notification sound doesn't work upon installation </summary>
			<description>I noticed after installation that when I receive messages, it didn't make a sound, it only flashed the notification light. I go to Settings -> Notifications, and I can see "Sound = Argon" is displayed. I press on 'Sound', which takes me to the sound selection list, but here there is none selected. I now select Argon from the list, back in settings it says "Sound = Argon" as before, but from now the app is making notification sounds. My colleague also had the same problem.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/TextSecurePreferences.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/f4fe024e503f87a5fea770a904b0f466c91a4834</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3102">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Date format does not respect locale </summary>
			<description>Currently TS seems to display all dates in the format MMM d, yyyy irrespective of the locale. The dates are translated correctly though. Here's some information about date formats in various regions: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Date_format_by_country TS 2.13.0 This issue does not depend on whether you have changed the system language or TS language. Neither work.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/DateUtils.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/message_details_header.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/c4f9bc2b5efaa6cbde1ff4202fa7be2e99315e7e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2585">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>don't inflate Emoji pane with the rest of the layout </summary>
			<description>Migrate the Emoji pane inflation to a ViewStub so it's only inflated when set to visible. Will knock off ~100ms when creating a conversation view.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/emoji_drawer_stub.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/9f804047f56ad207f25c71f52c37ab4eadf26efd</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3696">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>TS crashes while updating database after upgrade to 2.23 </summary>
			<description>See log: https://gist.github.com/1baa4ebc4f865ef3f3a1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/crypto/storage/TextSecurePreKeyStore.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/905b4f0a6bc85742c8901c9fee738dc44ea012e8</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2239">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>TextSecure randomly pops up </summary>
			<description>I can't nail down why TS does this. Sometimes, when I unlock the phone or exit an app, TextSecure will pop up asking for my password. When it does this, my finger is no where near the TS icon. Log follows: Device : LGE Nexus 5 (hammerhead)</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ApplicationPreferencesActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ActionBarListActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_list_activity.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/share_activity.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/0ff99258acd8e125ae902ff749f93e05c6f8ecb0</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1532">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Back Stack Issues </summary>
			<description>If I click back on a message, I often see the same message multiple times. A single message should only be in the back stack once. Also after clicking a notification, clicking back should return you to your previous app, now cycle you through all activity of TextSecure.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationFragment.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/1443d846c4b151b4e8d7440a1560aa688c19e6e4</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1526">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>TouchWiz notifications </summary>
			<description>Hi there. Just started using this great app. It's replaced my main Texting app on my S3. If I receive a text message I do get a notification in the bar but I'm used to the notification showing on the icon that is locked at the bottom of the screen and also it shows a new message next to the shortcut icon on the lock screen. It would have a little 1,2,3 or 4 next to the icon if I'd received 1,2,3 or 4 messages. This has been a common feature for all messaging apps I've ever had. I don't hardly ever check the notification bar so I've already missed several messages today due to this and it's only my first day using the app.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/1d0c9536fc5bb4954501b763f81e0c5a7d1995e0</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3331">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>image thumbnails disappearing </summary>
			<description>tested on 5fe7c68. image thumbnails are disappearing from the conversation view frequently, ends up looking like this. I can reproduce this by adding an image attachment and not sending it to a thread that already contains images in view, or just sending an image.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationItem.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/11613ad69f744f5fa6d9a303fa53b558a00fc29c</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3053">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Sending a deleted image gets stuck in pending state </summary>
			<description>This came up in #3046 briefly. Sometimes when you delete a picture it will leave around ghost thumbnails that are visible in the system gallery and also in TS attachment gallery. This can lead to the following issue if you try to send the deleted image: Delete a picture that's on your device with shell or a file manager (or create a ghost thumbnail in some other way) Attach that picture to a TS message using the attachment gallery's Recent tab (the gallery does not know that the picture was deleted) You will get a missing thumbnail icon Tap send TS will create an "empty" message that gets stuck in a pending state for eternity If you try to do the same in Google Hangouts you will get a 'Can't find picture' notification and you cannot send the image. TextSecure should also check if the file exists and not trust the gallery viewer. .gif demonstration: TS 2.12.0, stock Android 5.1 and Android 4.0.4</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/PushMediaSendJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/e51e5cdfd49ec7fc36695653ad60a232d07a520e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3536">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>new conversation incorrectly displayed as unread </summary>
			<description>start conversation with A send message to A receive message from A back out to the conversation list UI notice that your conversation with A is shown as unread</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/849c346a21f120593feab48eb4fe3356b6c7a3c4</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3330">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>crash bug on group... everything </summary>
			<description>tested on 5fe7c68 create a group update the group title crash bug debug log the stack traces seem to be an exact match to #3329, so likely the same bug but until that's certain I figure 2 issues is best.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/recipient_filter_item.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/message_details_header.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/12255ed453058d1100d068815018d556c8ab224f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5999">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Voice note recording cancels immediately if Android phone is set to Arabic language </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates, only RTL language issue is (#4714) and did not see this in voice note issues read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description Voice note recording to other Signal user does not record and cancels immediately if phone language is set to Arabic Steps to reproduce Set phone language to Arabic Open thread with a Signal contact Press mic to record voice message Actual result: Nothing records. option immediately closes Expected result: Record and send voice note Screenshots Device info Device: Samsung Galaxy S7 Android version: 3.25.3 Signal version: 6.0.1 Link to debug log https://gist.github.com/26a9adbe482848aa98499c648e0d6e1d</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable-ldrtl-xxhdpi/ic_keyboard_arrow_left_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_input_panel.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/InputPanel.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-ldrtl-hdpi/ic_keyboard_arrow_left_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-ldrtl-xhdpi/ic_keyboard_arrow_left_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-ldrtl-xxxhdpi/ic_keyboard_arrow_left_grey600_24dp.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/MicrophoneRecorderView.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/4dae4444bc588cb4f8d010edc2a70670163c0e48</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5755">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>'Disappears' in message_details_header.xml is hardcoded </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description The string 'Disappears' in the message details is hardcoded and cannot get translated. See https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/blob/0a569676f7a57144374a24faef566b2ca3233290/res/layout/message_details_header.xml#L87 Steps to reproduce Open conversation Select message Open message details Actual result: String always shows up in English Expected result: String should be translatable Device info Device: LG Nexus 5X Android version: 7.00 Signal version: 3.20.1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/message_details_header.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/e3da0ac908fb15d0ed3243d9f4ccfdeee7f88339</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3324">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Display app version in settings dialogue </summary>
			<description>The version number is not displayed within the TextSecure app. I suggest to display it at the bottom of the settings dialogue. Please let me know if I have missed something.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/preferences/AdvancedPreferenceFragment.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/155cbf686d59cd0172debc000c6883741b8e84a5</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1916">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>MMS Crash Report </summary>
			<description>Most frequent crash in the Play console right now: java.lang.RuntimeException: An error occured while executing doInBackground()</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/ApnDatabase.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/7316f176747289a509abfe7493bf9fec385df339</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3118">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>appcompat stack overflow </summary>
			<description>E/AndroidRuntime(13775): java.lang.StackOverflowError: stack size 8MB</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/values/themes.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ReceiveKeyActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/4011208db339464222f634eca88376d905b94fcb</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2548">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Missing notifications in Priority Mode / Lollipop </summary>
			<description>When I enable "Priority" mode in Lollipop, the phone won't ring/vibrate, as expected. But I wanted to enable the "ring for starred contacts", for messages as well as incoming calls. It works with the AOSP messaging app, but it doesn't work with TS. Is there a way to fix this? Thx! TextSecure 2.5.3 / LG G3 (d855) / CyanogenMod 12 App state: Push registered, incoming SMS enabled (default app), outgoing SMS enabled</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi-v11/icon_notification.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/contacts/ContactPhotoFactory.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi-v9/icon_notification.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi-v11/icon_notification.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>res/values/dimens.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi-v11/icon_notification.png</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi-v11/icon_notification.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/BitmapUtil.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi-v9/icon_notification.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/NotificationState.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/64fc83326f0cd0724cf1717ed115907fb1277f7a</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1055">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>drafts should be marked and moved to top of list </summary>
			<description>the message drafts should be automatically moved to the top of the message-list and be marked somehow, i.e. get another color or a text "Draft"</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/ThreadDatabase.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/f5724795cf1ced0360a02338c25491629527a3eb</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2945">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Long-pressing emoji backspace deletes only one character </summary>
			<description>Another lovely emoji keyboard related issue: If you want to remove ten characters with the emoji drawer's backspace you have to tap it ten times. Long press does not work. Compare to the regular keyboards' backspace which you can tap and hold to remove everything at once. Tested with: TS 2.11.0, Android 5.0.1, Android 4.0.4</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/EmojiDrawer.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/emoji_drawer.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/RepeatableImageKey.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/72f3f79016ae435951a2b2c938499008e4ca70b9</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5637">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>InviteReminder from an SMS intent for a phone number displays the contact name from the previous InviteReminder </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description InviteReminder from an SMS intent for a phone number displays the contact name from the previous InviteReminder Steps to reproduce Open Android Dialer, choose call history tab. Click on a recent phone call you've had with a contact that has a name, (let's say "ContactName"), but that you have not used signal with, and select "Send a message" Signal opens and displays the invite reminder: "Take your conversation with ContactName to the next level." (from InviteReminder.java) Open Android Dialer, choose call history tab. Click on a recent phone call you've had with that has just a phone number listed with no contact name (let's say "PhoneNumber"), but that you have not used signal with, and select "Send a message" Signal opens and displays the invite reminder: "Take your conversation with ContactName to the next level." (from InviteReminder.java) Actual result: The InviteReminder displays the ContactName from the previous conversation. Expected result: The previous ContactName is not in the InivteReminder. It looks like the InviteReminder is generally not displayed for SMS conversations with phone numbers (no contact name), so perhaps do not display the InviteReminder in this situation. Screenshots Device info Device: Nexus 5X Android version: 7.0 Signal version: 3.17.0 Link to debug log Not included, but please let me know if you need one. 👍 1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/63f7faf5bbe95cdbac80af3a0f307aa2d6904d27</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2372">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>share / add attachment: picture == > crash </summary>
			<description>same problem still existing! .... was closed on thread #2248 (i didnt know if should open a new one again or post in closed. couldnt find in guidelines) what happened there on the closed thread? i dont see the progress. cheers Device : Samsung GT-I9305 (m3xx) Android: omni_i9305-userdebug 4.4.4 KTU84P 440 test-keys App : TextSecure 2.4.2 when i send a picture from gallery / or as attachment out of TS or from my camera. it crashes. can someone confirm this? log: https://gist.github.com/d0195640abc36b4f8cf5</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/MediaPreviewActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/b88e470594a8f76b02ef1cce9b554f0b4f0f1748</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3044">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>NPE: ThumbnailView, tap preview icon of media message draft </summary>
			<description>encountered this while running an unmodified debug build of 27a5b7d, steps to reproduce: open conversation click add attachment select any picture tap on preview before sending crash crash log >> https://gist.github.com/rhodey/b791b99d3efb34d423b4 NPE occurs on same line as #3042 04-23 10:42:50.356    2532-2532/org.thoughtcrime.securesms.sushi D/AndroidRuntime﹕ Shutting down VM</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ThumbnailView.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a330f6f689cee41df2d4ca63b023b07c9a1e0592</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3051">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Thumbnails not rendering </summary>
			<description>Built a RC and tried sending a few images. This happens every so often, where the entire message bubble (except for the arrow) fails to render:</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/MmsDatabase.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/26c4d746d206a57687e90d5778fe2f090e868408</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3086">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>delete thread on new conversation appears to do nothing </summary>
			<description>2.12.0 from play store. unexpected behavior 00: click the new conversation button select a contact for which no conversation exists options menu > delete thread > yes nothing happens unexpected behavior 01: click the new conversation button select a contact for which no conversation exists create a draft but don't leave the conversation options menu > delete thread > yes nothing happens the behavior I expect is to be returned to the conversation list view and not see any sign of the previous new conversation, this goes well if a draft is saved for the conversation like so: click the new conversation button select a contact for which no conversation exists create a draft go back to conversation list view reopen the new conversation options menu > delete thread > yes thread deleted and returned to conversation list view</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/b6e241b0dcbded2fdddb27373c8e442258c8b508</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5144">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Names with accents (diacritics) wrong sorted in contact list </summary>
			<description>Contact list displays names with accents in the wrong order resulting in people named "Álvaro" being sorted after "Zacarías" (not able to attach image at the moment). I think COLLATE LOCALIZED in https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/blob/master/src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/contacts/ContactsDatabase.java (line 150) will do the trick but i'm not a programmer. According to what I've found: [LOCALIZED] It instructs SQLite to sort non-ASCII characters appropriately. Chars with diacritics (some call them accents) have higher byte codes than the character Z, so a plain ASCII sort wouldn't fit to many foreign languages. For example, the capital A char's byte code is 0x41 and the capital Z char's is 0x5A. Then we have the Á (capital A accute) which code in Unicode is 0x00C1. So a plain byte code sort would result the Á to be after the Z. But in languages that have this kind of characters the convention is to put those with diacritics as if they didn't have the diacritic. So the Á should be together with the plain A, at least before B. And to illustrate, we have below a list of names sorted using their bytecode: Brenda</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/contacts/ContactsDatabase.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/1b97756b05c810795c12db18510dad8c0f063c22</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3441">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>CrashBrowser: NPE </summary>
			<description>java.lang.NullPointerException: Attempt to invoke virtual method 'android.net.Uri org.thoughtcrime.securesms.recipients.Recipients.getRingtone()' on a null object reference</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/2fb9806f36bc9fffbff5c7879dcf3fdfe2c067c7</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3327">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>screen security setting does not apply to "submit debug log" UI </summary>
			<description>enable screen security Settings > Advanced > Submit debug log open recent activities view notice that screen security didn't do its thing</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/BaseActionBarActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/PassphraseRequiredActionBarActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a930ec540412e65a9016563c8e259f73fc55107e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3333">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>checkbox when adding contacts overlapped by scrolling click zone </summary>
			<description>tested on 82d7300 create a TS group with person A tap update group tap the weird plus icon next to the add member edit text try to check the box next to TS user person B notice it ripples in a really cool way but also it's really difficult to check that box guessing this came from bd2e984</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/PushContactSelectionListFragment.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/push_contact_selection_list_item.xml</file>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/58be07f5b17886ab6b13e4e8d561f4419f93e172</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5959">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>"Our Signal safety numbers:" string appears twice with some Share targets </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description With some Share targets, such as Twitter DMs, the string "Our Signal safety numbers:" appears twice, followed by the safety number. Steps to reproduce Go into "Conversation Settings > Verify safety numbers" Press the Share button in the upper right corner Share via Twitter DM Actual result: The string appears twice. Expected result: The string should only appear once. Screenshots Device info Signal version: 3.23.0</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/VerifyIdentityActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/57cdbaedd646529ede41749fce0f16e1fe0b5ea3</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5965">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>3.25.0 introduced probably unintended UI changes </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description 6308e64 introduced this, let the screenshots speak for themselves. Besides the changes you can see in the screenshots the animation when you send a message and the new bubble appears changed slightly, I think. Screenshots A wild Signal icon appears in... ... NewConversationActivity ... RecipientPreferenceActivity ... InviteActivity ... GiphyActivity Mind the gap between back arrow and recipient, before 6308e64 After 6308e64 👍 1 😄 1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ContactFilterToolbar.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/contact_filter_toolbar.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/giph/ui/GiphyActivityToolbar.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ContactSelectionActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/RecipientPreferenceActivity.java</file>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/InviteActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/video/EncryptedMediaDataSource.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/contact_selection_activity.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/NewConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/4ff8de0ca8b95d4b1ee4e89a14fce2dc9340258b</commit_url>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/71f8e9eb31d798051567ac021ef8c9b2dc840139</commit_url>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/d280604f1fe2ce9a5a8d85dff0c6f55eeb4c7f09</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="6061">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Crash after sharing xlsx as jpg </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description Signal crashes after sending a shared Excel-file (xlsx) which has been renamed to end with jpg. Afterwards it can't be used anymore. Steps to reproduce Rename a xyz.xlsx (Excel-File) to xyz.xlsx.jpg Share xyz.xlsx.jpg via signal to a contact Press the send button (The app crashes) Try to reopen the app Actual result: The app crashes in step 3 and can't be opened afterwards (step 4). The apps can only be restored to work with deleting all data via the android settings. Expected result: The best would be support xlsx files to be supported. The minimum requirement in my opinion is that the app rejects shared files that are not supported and doesn't keep crashing in this case. Screenshots n.a. Device info Device: Aquaris M5 Android version: 6.0.1 Signal version: 3.26.2 Link to debug log A debug log can't be captured as signal crashes immediately after any restart attemp.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/BitmapUtil.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/4461ebf6620ea41ef9b117e301f7a1ae62735271</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5583">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Signal freezes on Android 7 Preview 5 when trying to add an attachment </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description Signal was working without problems on latest Android 6.0.1 on my Nexus 6. Today I've "dirty" flashed the latest Android 7.0 Preview 5 image. I have wiped the cache partition afterwards. Signal is working on Android 7 Preview 5, but when I click the paperclip button to add an attachment, Signal freezes immediately. The blinking cursor in the text input field stops blinking and the app does not respond to any further input. After closing the app by swiping it off the recent apps list, Signal can be opened again. The same happens if I select the respective menu item instead of clicking the paperclip button. Steps to reproduce Open Signal app. Enter a conversation. Click on paperclip button or select respective menu item to add an attachment to the message. Actual result: Signal hangs/freezes immediately. The cursor stops blinking and the app does not respond to any further input. Expected result: The "attachment selection dialogue" is shown, so I can select an attachment to be added to the message. Device info Device: Motorola Nexus 6 Android version: 7.0 Preview 5 (NPD90G) Signal version: 3.16.0 Link to debug log https://gist.github.com/anonymous/a8c508d1b94d8be848149cd9025fccda 👍 1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/AttachmentTypeSelector.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/716ed251bca520c678052e3e0eed5089512a7f97</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1722">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Menu item to send a TextSecure installation link </summary>
			<description>For easier spread of TextSecure, it might be good to offer a menu item in unencrypted SMS conversations that starts the message editor with TextSecure's Google Play link (and maybe a text like "Please install the following for encrypted communication:"). The menu item should have a name like "Ask for encrypted communication", although this might be too long.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/menu/conversation_insecure_no_push.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/menu/conversation_insecure.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/426c56c77dc92acd54be26d11f87f88469631c9d</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5949">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Crash loop on attempting to send image </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description A friend tried to send me a just then taken photo. On preparing the image for sending, signal enters a crash loop. The application becomes unsuable. The crash loop can be broken by disabling wifi and mobile internet and deleting the faulty multimedia message. Symptoms are similar to Bug #5310, the difference being that on my friends phone the error log shows an OutOfMemoryError which does not appear there. Btw: larger images sent without problems. Even though the image displays fine everywhere else, it might be faulty. Steps to reproduce Download 20161210_133710.jpg from dropbox link below to phone Check sha256 hashsum to verify it is indeed the same image that crashes Singnal on my friends Samsung Enable Wifi / Mobile Internet Send Image to another contact using Signal Actual result: Signal crashes repeatedly every few seconds when not in use or when entering the application and becomes unusable. Expected result: Signal should catch all image-processing errors and not crash. Steps to recover from error Disable Wifi / Mobile Internet Enter Signal, delete faulty Image / Message to stop Singal from crashing Image that crashes signal + Versioninfo https://www.dropbox.com/sh/ou6tintrxzw6okd/AABYd3GrkjnkS1SH0dgGl3oZa?dl=0 Device info Device: samsung SM-G900F (kltexx) Android version: 6.0.1 Signal version: 3.24.1 Link to debug log https://gist.github.com/anonymous/4257a85bab5f738c8496329c80d5d655</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/MediaConstraints.java</file>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/AttachmentManager.java</file>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/MediaPreviewActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/zooming_image_view.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/subsampling/AttachmentBitmapDecoder.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ZoomingImageView.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/subsampling/AttachmentRegionDecoder.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/d2be49af42eeebc888816904b1f765090be175ac</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2940">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Visible glitch when toggling between keyboard and built-in Emoji drawer </summary>
			<description>Hello, when toggling between the keyboard and the TextSecure Emoji drawer, the TextSecure Emoji drawer appears above the keyboard for a brief momen and "fades" into the keyboard, which looks like a glitch and is uneasy on the eyes. In Telegram for Android, that does not happen. In Telegram for Android, when toggling between the built-in Emoji drawer and the keyboard, the toggle happens instantly, the Emoji drawer instantly replaces the keyboard, without any transition or whatever, which looks much smoother. In TextSecure it currently looks buggy and is quite uneasy on the eyes. Could you please fix it? Regards</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/dimens.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/emoji_drawer.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/fa62b9bde224341e0c2d43c0694fc10c4df7336f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3337">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Notification sound incorrectly plays when viewing a conversation from recipient </summary>
			<description>With my Nexus 6 (Android 5.1) on priority mode TextSecure does not play notification sounds. This is correct. However, with my phone set up as above, if I send a message to someone and remain viewing that conversation, TextSecure will incorrectly play the notification sound if that person replies to me.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a698477e10d59602bf5da7f9902421bda82ef739</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1483">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Date and time not readable in Dark Theme </summary>
			<description>The date and timestamp is not easily readable in the darktheme, because the text is too dark. It' grey on dark grey, green on dark green or blue on dark blue. Esp. on displays with high resolution (full hd), it is to small to read with this little contrast.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/values/themes.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/9ffd84ce05f10d14c1e33f7adb642016ce4ec34e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3525">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>TS Media Messages Received Timestamps Report Different Times </summary>
			<description>Sometimes I receive an MMS (over push) when I am offline; when I finally come back online, I get the MMS message with two different received timestamps. My guess is that one timestamp corresponds to the time sent, and the other time stamp corresponds to the time received. This seems to be confusing and unnecessary information for the user, who probably only cares about when the message is sent, and doesn't understand why the time stamps are different. Device info: Sony Xperia Z3 Tablet Compact, stock android 4.4.4, TextSecure 2.21.0? (I compiled from b7492eb) App state: Push registered, incoming SMS disabled, outgoing SMS fully disabled Debug logs: https://gist.github.com/anonymous/98fe3fb59609cd429909 Example here where the last picture received has a timestamp difference of about 4 minutes, because that's how long I was offline. Both of these screenshots were taken within a minute of each other.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/model/MessageRecord.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationItem.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/ThreadDatabase.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/fe5e101463670041fe6923ff76e8ce7e35cd9d1d</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1858">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>please add option to hide message sender and the contence of a message in notification bar. </summary>
			<description>hi, please add a option to hide the sender of a message and the message contence when the notification appears in the notification bar. in other words it would now say new message from john smith and what he wrote. what I want is just 1 new message that's it nothing about sender or what's in the message. thank you for all you do.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/NotificationItem.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/SingleRecipientNotificationBuilder.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/AttachmentDownloadJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/f8bb065ffd0a76417c91e6df2ad8fcb49a9ee165</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3295">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>units </summary>
			<description>On the textSecure panel showing the list of threads, each of them has a field showing the time elapsed since the last message. typically I read something like "11 mins". I wonder what the s after min stands for. Unit for minute is min, and units do not take plural form. Unfortunately I must say that this trend of putting plural mark to units is more and more common in the US, and it appears that it is getting more common in other countries as well. Spreading that nonsense is definitely not good so I suggest that the "plural unit issue" be taken care of as soon as possible. Check also for the hour, I am pretty sure that soon some "hrs" will show up. "h" would actually be the best, while "hr" being also accepted. Thank you</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/DateUtils.java</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/570f79d91ad027939c8190a95436b3749793c7b7</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2996">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>"There are four lights!" or How conversation list's 'select all' disregards search results </summary>
			<description>Go to your conversation list Search for some subset of your conversations Tap and hold to select at least one of the conversations from the search results Now tap 'select all' from the top right corner TS will select all of your conversations instead of just all the search results (6. If you want to live dangerously try to delete the selected messages by tapping the trash bin. It will remove all conversations. This proves that it really selects all conversations and not just misrepresent the number of selected messages.) A .gif demonstration (does not strictly follow the above steps): TS 2.11.1, Android 5.0.1 and also 4.0.4</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationListAdapter.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/cdd7a1042a9638bb9fddadd8815dc8cbb3d7f090</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5579">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Duplicate messages being received during standard TextSecure messaging (non group). </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description In standard two device messaging (signal messages, not SMS), one user receives some messages twice, however the sender doesn't see the duplicate message in their history. The log shows that around the same time, the MessageRetrievalService logs a time-out, causing it to loop around for another go. In reality both attempts seem to result in a message being rendered. Steps to reproduce Use two devices (Nexus 5 and Nexus 5x) Proceed to have a secured (TextSecure) conversation Actual result: Nexus 5 receives some messages twice. Expected result: Nexus 5 should receive exactly one message for each message the Nexus 5x sends to it. Screenshots Device info Device: LGE Nexus 5 (hammerhead) Android version: 6.0.1 (2960889, MOB30P) Signal version: Signal 3.16.0 Link to debug log https://gist.github.com/anonymous/177442603d179b543fc9ef6ac7c58ba3#file-cat-log-L229</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/MessagingDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/EncryptingSmsDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/groups/GroupMessageProcessor.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/SmsDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/MmsDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/MmsDownloadJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/7e51d61c7900e9d57c15eb6a6d595103bfdb7f79</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2558">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>notifications for group messages </summary>
			<description>when multiple people post new messages in a group chat, the notification on android assigns them all to the first person that posted. Only when I open the app, I learn that they are from multiple people. Maybe it would be more straightforward to show the group name in notifications instead?</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/NotificationItem.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/SingleRecipientNotificationBuilder.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/3b80e3554732865e42406e36f4bf38bef661af5a</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3646">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>TextSecure 2.22 crashes when opening from Notification </summary>
			<description>Log: https://gist.github.com/anonymous/7e3cd1b9fff04fcd6beb TextSecure 2.22 Sony Xperia P CM 12</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/5c3b96a947253f7d7a0962b08a4d744f09ce20be</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3120">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>message notification contact photo solid white for contact with no picture </summary>
			<description>built from 4ad9d6b running on my Nexus 5, Lollipop 5.1 in the conversation list view contact "lol myself" has no associated image, so an avatar is generated, the output is pink and the letter "l". however when I receive a message form "lol myself" the generated avatar is not shown in the message notification, in its place is only white.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/BitmapUtil.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/e62528d3e2e18677a944a8575acf2b2f62f16c34</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3134">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Cursor not shown when typing a message </summary>
			<description>You know the little pulsing bar that appears when writing something in a text box? (I'm sure i thas a name but I can't think of a better description right now). Since 2.14.1 (probably 2.14) it has disappeared from textsecure. This obviously makes it hard and uncomfortable to write messages.. I like textsecure, and I appreciate the effort you're putting into it, really. But do you even test the app before releasing updates? Missing commas that screw the phones and make us lose messages, huge usability problems that would've taken 10 seconds to notice... I mean... of course it's human to forget a comma or introduce bugs, we all know it. The problem is that testing should be considered fundamental, even when you have beta testers. Beta testers are supposed to find smaller problems, not sacrifice their product for the sake of bugs. That's what the developers should be doing. Apologies if it sounds rude, and thanks again.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ComposeText.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/488767550e7d5fd3b322adaadf19802122dacc7b</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1904">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>MMSCs using proxies not working </summary>
			<description>I don't like MMS :/ CM11 Trying to send with wifi enabled: --------- beginning of /dev/log/main</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/IncomingMmsConnection.java</file>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/ApnDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/MmsPreferencesActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/89fb80fcc5e4c35169840877d98c599006f9628d</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2943">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Where are the old text-only smileys? </summary>
			<description>Why did you remove the old text based smileys? I don't like all this emoji crap and preferred the other ones.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>assets/emoji-3.png</file>
			<file>assets/emoji-4.png</file>
			<file>assets/emoji-1.png</file>
			<file>assets/emoji-2.png</file>
			<file>assets/emoji-0.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_emoticons.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/94085798621f4036454fef2a4096ad7588a80793</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2957">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Emojis appear dissected / cut off / stretched </summary>
			<description>Hello, the Emojis randomly appear dissected / cut off / stretched on the TextSecure Emoji drawer. It happens regardless of the system font size, as you can see in the following screenshots: System font size @ minimum: System font size @ medium: System font size @ maximum: So, I don't know what triggers it. It actually even happened the very first time I opened the Emoji drawer after having upgraded from TextSecure 2.9.3 to TextSecure 2.10.2. Closing TextSecure via the task manager and then reopening it seems to solve it at first, but the issue seems to randomly reappear. Happening on LG G2 with stock 4.4.2 KitKat. Could you please fix it? Regards</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiProvider.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/BitmapUtil.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/103686f89b3a5b987ec174d0ab1487e57bdb7003</commit_url>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/21341c5213cf4f8f150ec68b50524cf16088bca4</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2764">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Selecting failed messages is impossible </summary>
			<description>-send a message and make it fail (somehow) -try to select the message to delete it The only workaround I found is to select another message first, then select the failed one, deselect the first one and then delete the failed one Thank you</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationItem.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a712875830f817ac4d29da0630c9da153761fcce</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3240">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Make the emoji panel back color theme dependent </summary>
			<description>In other words: Turn off f the light for the li'l fellas' home, when it's dark outside 🌞🌚</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_objects_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_nature_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_emoticons_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_places_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_nature.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_objects_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_places_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_nature_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_nature_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_symbols_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_people_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_places_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_objects_dark.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_symbols_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_objects_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_symbols_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_people_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/values/themes.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_emoticons.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiPageModel.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_people_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_people_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_people_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_recents_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_symbols_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_recents_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_recent.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_recents_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_objects_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_objects_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_emoticons_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_places_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_objects_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_emoticons_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_places_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_symbols_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_emoticons_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_recent_dark.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_emoticons_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiDrawer.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_recents_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_symbols_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_nature_dark.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_nature_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_nature_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_people_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_nature_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_people.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_recents_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/StaticEmojiPageModel.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_people_dark.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_emoticons_dark.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_symbol_dark.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_recents_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_places_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_places.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/colors.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/emoji_drawer.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_emoticons_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_symbols_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_recents_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/RecentEmojiPageModel.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_people_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_nature_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_objects_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiPages.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiView.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_emoticons_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_emoticons_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_places_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_objects.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_emoji_nature_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_symbol.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_symbols_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_emoji_objects_activated_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_recents_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_emoji_places_normal_dark.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/emoji_category_places_dark.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_emoji_people_activated_dark.png</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/ae4f6b1dd4af6b8dce07d6dfe4024ed95f738511</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3042">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>NPE: ThumbnailView, tap preview icon when file not found </summary>
			<description>encountered this while running an unmodified debug build of 27a5b7d sequence of events were: send a bunch of text messages send a bunch of media messages do the same while screwing around with airplane mode attach image image preview is an error icon (may have been ic_action_warning_red or ic_missing_thumbnail_picture, can't remember) click on error image preview crash I then tried to reproduce by simply returning to the convo and reattaching the same image, crash again. Did this a few more times and once the image preview was entirely blank (but still took up the space it should), clicked on that too, crash. While in this crashable state I attempted to reproduce this using a different attachment, no crash. Thinking it may have had something to do with cache I tried another different image that definitely should not have been in cache, also no crash. Eventually through some multi-step process I can't recall I was able to stop the error image from showing up for that one attachment and thus stop the crashing. debug log >> https://gist.github.com/anonymous/266cafd4ee10f5f3e380 crash E/AndroidRuntime(14933): FATAL EXCEPTION: main</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ThumbnailView.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a330f6f689cee41df2d4ca63b023b07c9a1e0592</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2413">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Wrong default MMS settings for Slovenian provider Tušmobil </summary>
			<description>My sister's phone wasn't able to send/recieve MMS messages so I checked things out. When I entered the manual settings that I copied from the default SMS/MMS app on her phone it worked. I believe that one setting is set wrong and all the others are ok. provider: Tušmobil WRONG: MMS Proxy: 91.185.221.085 OK: MMS Proxy: 91.185.221.85 I wanted to open Pull request and correct the setting myself but wasn't sure which is the right file to edit.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/0b8430ff43556816955e7c90e272b0a31d0759eb</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5817">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Group avatar stuck to some old version after change </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description It seems changing the group avatar has a weird issue where it's stuck to some old (the last successfully changed?) group avatar. It's kinda weird that the old one can be from an entirely different group :/ Also it's not just a local (cache) issue. The wrong avatar gets actually sent to every member. Steps to reproduce change the group avatar to a new photo Actual result: group avatar is stuck to some old avatar (possibly from another group) Expected result: group avatar should change to the new image Device info Device: bq Aquaris E4.5 and Nvidia K1 Android version: 5.0 and 6.0.1 Signal version: 3.21.0 Link to debug log https://gist.github.com/f7514791daed60132fd95e57d387e236 This is kinda shitty report. Would be great if someone tried to reproduce. I have this issue on two devices.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/GroupCreateActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/9d3b764fec52280305ddb6d4d678aafc8efe73b0</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1481">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>strange menu item text </summary>
			<description>there is "Get scanned to compare" (just below "Scan to compare") which was not understandable to me (as a non-native speaker, but I suspect native speaker might have issues, too). suggestion: show QR code (to compare)</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/VerifyIdentityActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ViewIdentityActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/menu/key_scanning.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/12957d96e0c885c73e1ac607d37d9cbd99e955a2</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5910">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>incorrect labling of button </summary>
			<description>Dear Devs, First kindly accept my kind gratitude for including the voice note feature in Signal Private Messanger for Android. Here, I am reporting a minor issue which can easily be fixed. The Record button or mic button is improperly labled. In the left of the bottom part of the window, there is the 'emoji' button. then, there is the edit box followed by the 'toggle attachment' button. After that, there is the record button I think. but our screen reader (Talkback) announces it as "toggle attachment" button. That's why, we visually challenged persons are getting two 'toggle attachment' buttons, which is a bit confusing. Kind regards, Pradip 👍 2</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_input_panel.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/2197d77ffc21a37934ffe1d4a57d62ca35137f17</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="665">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Alphanumeric addresses in SMS messages </summary>
			<description>My carrier and some other companies sometimes send SMS with alphanumeric addresses. When TextSecure receives them, it shows sender as Anonymous. Also, it won't import them from system database (i. e. SMS will not show in TextSecure in any way). I have saved few such messages on my phone (Galaxy Nexus) and I know a tiny bit about Android development, so if there anything I can check/send to help resolve the issue, I will be glad to help.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/recipients/RecipientFactory.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/transport/SmsTransport.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/addea8d3400a352ce7bb152f99527e72a8e716ee</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3434">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Unblock crashes if custom ringtone is set </summary>
			<description>Steps to reproduce: Set a costum rintone for a specific contact Block this contact Unblock the contact from the conversation view (button wich replaces input field) TS crashes log: https://gist.github.com/anonymous/31c17bf711aae49c3b46 Additional notes: Does not happen if no custom ringtone is set. In spite of the crash "unblocking" is successful.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/RecipientPreferenceActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a7f63ed9a378075811008a21030c430167ec8707</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2851">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>CrashBrowser: MMS NPE </summary>
			<description>java.lang.NullPointerException</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/SmilUtil.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/5cb94f02b3587b0649bff667b4d1c351ee59949e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1343">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>In dark theme, text too dark when starting new conversation from "+" </summary>
			<description>Enable Dark Theme Press "+" to start new conversation a. Notice that "TEXTSECURE USERS" and "ALL CONTACTS" text is still very dark. b. Even text showing the contact names and numbers are fairly dark still. Should probably be a fair amount brighter for all the text and lines between things. Using Galaxy S4, Auto dimming.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/push_contact_selection_list_header.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/themes.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/7349378d8d2bef654f0ab6b93410be7467fb968d</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1141">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Archive </summary>
			<description>I see the option of deleting messages and limiting conversation limits in the settings, so I don't know if the practice of regularly deleting messages is a practice in security. But I like to keep an archive of my messages, separate from my "current" messages. I think this is a pretty common feature in most messaging platforms.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_archive_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>...ble/conversation_list_item_background.xml</file>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>res/menu/conversation_list_batch.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/contact_selection_list_item.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_list_item_action.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/menu/conversation_list_batch_unarchive.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_unarchive_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/conversation_list_item_read_background.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_archive_white_36dp.png</file>
			<file>...v21/conversation_list_item_background.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-v21/conversation_list_item_read_background.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/BindableConversationListItem.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_list_item_view.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_unarchive_white_36dp.png</file>
			<file>res/menu/conversation_list_batch_archive.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_unarchive_white_36dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_unarchive_white_36dp.png</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationFragment.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_archive_white_48dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_unarchive_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_unarchive_white_36dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_unarchive_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/colors.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/themes.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xhdpi/ic_unarchive_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_unarchive_white_36dp.png</file>
			<file>res/menu/conversation.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-hdpi/ic_archive_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/dimens.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_unarchive_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-mdpi/ic_archive_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable/rounded_rectangle.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_list_fragment.xml</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxxhdpi/ic_archive_white_24dp.png</file>
			<file>res/drawable-xxhdpi/ic_archive_white_24dp.png</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/2ab0029d4929e020414ab56e5afdfddc3a695726</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2850">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>CrashBrowser: MMS IllegalArgumentException </summary>
			<description>java.lang.IllegalArgumentException: Username may not be null</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/LegacyMmsConnection.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/796c5de5d577b6aafc6f829b76f70439a7b23b7d</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3347">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Picture message failure </summary>
			<description>I am running into a problem trying to send a picture on my 1st Gen Moto X running 4.4.4. I'm using TextSecure 2.16.4 in data mode. I took a photo in potrait mode using both the camera app and the in-app option to take a photo. Both times the message will appear in the text window but fail to send. Here's a log from immediately after the failure https://gist.github.com/anonymous/52824d6ed48b2be2a32f I verified that I could send a different photo (in landscape mode) and captured another debug log here https://gist.github.com/anonymous/7f056f9973425195b26c I have tried closing and reopening TextSecure without success. It seems specific to this photo as other photos (both taken on the phone or from other sources) are able to be sent. I'm not sure if it's the subject (as other issues mentioned grass being hard to compress) or the orientation of the photo. This seems similar to #3070 or #3028. Also seems like this might have just recently been fixed in version 2.17. Sorry if this is a duplicate. Picture here</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>test/androidTest/java/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/BitmapUtilTest.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/BitmapUtil.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/f72cd5b0fffe2465b40213828a9214c8c2517715</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2703">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>[2.6.4] No notifications shown on new message receive </summary>
			<description>After updating to version 2.6.4 from 2.5.x via Google Play Store no notifications about new received messages were shown when application runs in the background. The notifications and the messages are only received when running the the foregound, which leads to missed messages. This is new with 2.6.4, I never had the problem with any previous version. Samsung GT-i9505 (jfltexx) Android 4.4.4 (KOT49H.I9505XXUGNK4) OS Host: SWDD6301 TextSecure 2.6.4</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/service/MessageRetrievalService.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/b77afa890368009007cfd658ad4bec3e22b9e868</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3623">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Landscape mode send button text not updated </summary>
			<description>Write text, switch send mode, go landscape . Only updates when there is no input on the compose field, or input got deleted afterwards</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/124d72801015a998b15f27776fe50ddae0dbd259</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3621">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>In the ConversationActivity, selected emoji do not match displayed emoji </summary>
			<description>Phone: Moto G 2014 TS version: commit 7593918 Steps to reproduce. Open coveation Click smiley face emoji button to pull emoji drawer Attempt to make a selection while the screen is scrolled down n > 2 rows Expected outcome: The selected emoji is displayed. Actual outcome: No emoji is displayed. Incorrect emoji is displayed. Example: While the emoji selection box is scrolled exactly two lines down, clicking fearful-face yields face-savouring-delicious-food, and clicking weary-face yields face-with-medical-mask. Further, with the box scrolled exactly three lines down, clicking fearful-face yields confounded-face.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiPopup.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiPageView.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/0af902b81c9d19a52889c526b48d5e6b9bfaf3d1</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="672">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Lower compression for sent pictures </summary>
			<description>It would be nice if pictures which are sent over the data channel aren't so highly compressed. 👍 3</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/PushMediaConstraints.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/BitmapUtil.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/b54a271a753fd31dcea77e258e5df5188f1da156</commit_url>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/23544fae8a259fcd38162a27aa53221175b4ab7e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3386">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>tile person images to denote group mms chats </summary>
			<description>When viewing the conversation list, all mms group conversation icons only display for THE FIRST PERSON listed in the group chat. If a image is available, it will display only one contact image, otherwise if an contact image is not available, the the first letter of the first contact's first name is shown. I would like to see group chat icons in the conversation list denoted with a tile view comprised of the group contacts (possibly up to 4 tiles). It seems the special TextSecure groups have a stock grey icon to denote those type of chats since they have a group title/name. For example, if there are 3 contacts in the group MMS (2 friends plus yourself) the visual icon on the conversation list would show a vertically split tile view of your contacts photo or the Letter of their first name if a photo is not available. For reference, is similar to the Google hangout view. [][] [][] [ __ ] [][] [][] Consider similar feature for the special TextSecure group icon. version 2.16.4</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/AvatarImageView.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ShareListItem.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/RecipientPreferenceActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationListItem.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/preferences/BlockedContactListItem.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/recipients/Recipients.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/4feedab02c0e63dd25ce4b80ad950b482e4dc502</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5046">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>invalid image causes crash </summary>
			<description>SVG attachment support in Signal-Android would be nice. Sending and receiving SVG files from Signal-Desktop works great, but on the Android client, they are not previewed and cannot be opened. Now the critical part: Even on the Android client, it is possible to select SVG files as image attachments. But when sending them, the app crashes and now I'm not able to open Signal-Andoid again. Each time I try to open the app, it crashes immediately.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/MediaConstraints.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/MediaUtil.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiProvider.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/AvatarDownloadJob.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/BitmapDecodingException.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/BitmapUtil.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/4a261bcf68ac94d48bba80e913b7773306d38cc7</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1397">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>unable to resolve static method 975: Landroid/provider/Telephony$Sms </summary>
			<description>cf log: http://hastebin.com/bepikemedo Just installed the latest version of TextSecure on my son's new phone: Wiko Ozzy running Android 4.2.2 http://fr.wikomobile.com/mobile.php?t=63&telephone-portable=WIKO-OZZY It crashed while we were setting up the application with the phone number. A subsequent restart allowed us to proceed just fine (though we hit another snag, cf forthcoming bug). W/dalvikvm( 6154): VFY: unable to resolve static method 975: Landroid/provider/Telephony$Sms;.getDefaultSmsPackage (Landroid/content/Context;)Ljava/lang/String;</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/RegistrationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/dff6997a6524d86a681a0d8c939653bebacb8453</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5898">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Disable audio controls in selection mode </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description Hitting audio controls in selection mode actually has an effect besides of selecting. Steps to reproduce Open a conversation with a voice note (audio attachment) Long-tap a message Hit audio controls (play button or slider) Actual result: Audio attachment starts playing or slider jumps to hit position. Expected result: The message should be (un)marked and the audio controls should ignore they were hit.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationItem.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/AudioView.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/970448d43d02b7fa947e3aaa7c17140de60eb25f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2891">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Alignment of the keyboard / Smiley switch for long texts </summary>
			<description>If you type a long message, the keyboard / Smiley switch gets aligned vertically in the middle, thereby moving upwards the longer your message is. Whatsapp etc. has a fixed position on the bottom, which makes it easier for unskilled users to notice it's position. 2.10.1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable-v21/touch_highlight_background.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/01bebf217642823810e878168d6f4703e8ce9bbf</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2488">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Mark/Select picture attachment at conversation - problems. </summary>
			<description>Hi folks, when i try to select an attachment (picture) at the conversation while pressing "ON" the picture, it gets marked but as soon i release my finger from the screen the picture automaticly gets unmarked. After repeating the following steps 5-6 times he finally catched my selection. BUT! When i mark next to the picture, on the blank screen, it gets marked immediately. U need a log for this?</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/drawable/conversation_item_background.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationAdapter.java</file>
			<file>res/drawable/conversation_item_background_dark.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/BindableConversationItem.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_fragment.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_item_received.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/themes.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_item_sent.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/99d3374d35b5027850fdc31c8a2620fb5f83fbf7</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5331">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>TextSecureAttachment.java Exception "No length specified!" </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates: maybe related to #3882 (closed / unresolved) read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports checked if maybe cyanogenmod 13.0 issue Bug description Every time after I start signal (after successfully entering my password) it loads my messages and immediately crashes. My android signal is linked to a signal chromium app (Chromium: 49.0.2623.87-1, Signal Private Messenger: 0.1.6) . Only android signal seems affected. Steps to reproduce Hard to tell. Occurred only once (5 minutes ago): send images in group chats via android signal wait until it crashes for the first time signal will now crash everytime after starting (after password input) with the following exception: 03-12 19:19:56.633  3542  3558 E AndroidRuntime: FATAL EXCEPTION: JobConsumer-1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/PushSendJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a6488b3652fbf34e74e6dd9c0ba1ac53d47948ec</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2462">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Coarse filtering can cause crashes </summary>
			<description>Weird one: java.lang.RuntimeException: An error occured while executing doInBackground()</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/Util.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/ThreadDatabase.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/797b296f3a347a0eb569a3bebdbcfdc3ef0d892e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2660">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>new message to <phone number> does not appear if incoming sms disabled </summary>
			<description>Currently, the recipient must be in the sender's contacts. Though only a minor inconvenience for those of us that do not wish to sync any personal information with Google's servers, it seems like a rather arbitrary restriction.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/contacts/ContactsDatabase.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/87760a795dbc4bef4dc4dc0f58d4c73998d6293e</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2853">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Crash on verify contact </summary>
			<description>This dialog is currently broken: I have a fix for the design issue (#2821) but I couldn't figure out why its crashing when you click on verify. I guess this happend after the routing logic commit 0ff9925     27147-27147/org.thoughtcrime.securesms E/AndroidRuntime﹕ FATAL EXCEPTION: main</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/VerifyIdentityActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/b8a231c40f1972f65bedce84b688e8b5bfbcc9c6</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2700">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Emoji pane losing history </summary>
			<description>Hi! Since version 2.6, TextSecure loses the emoji history (last used emojis) from time to time. Never happened before with older version. Thanks for your great work!</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/util/Emoji.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/f38bd7b18748b669b9924ed2af029bf42096e093</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="840">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Wrong image in chat preview </summary>
			<description>Hello, when I send an image, in the chat there is shown an image I sent before instead of the right one I just have sent. When it is clicked, the right one is shown in full screen. Even when I delete the conversation and I send a new image, the old wrong picture is shown in chat. (Fullscreen shows the right image). Does Deletion of conversation not delete data of the conversation? Greets</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/PartAuthority.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/PartUri.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/PartDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/MmsDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/ImageSlide.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/mms/IncomingMediaMessage.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/dc903e49af94de4339b90e1e757d5f2948536435</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5090">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Signal crashes when notification sound is set to "none" and in-conversation notifications are enabled. </summary>
			<description>Android 5.1 Signal 3.9.1 (also observed on previous versions - can't be more specific). https://gist.github.com/anonymous/291abefd9fa914074d60 If notification sound is set to "None" and "In-conversation notifications" are turned on Signal will crash whenever you receive a message while having the conversation open. This only occurs when the conversation the message is a part of is currently open. It doesn't occur if a different conversation is open or if Signal is in the background. When you re-open the app the message that caused the crash will display properly. This affects both Signal conversations and regular SMS conversations with Signal as the SMS client.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/4049b997ee7e985d9f70d7c5adcf12b80e609fa6</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3181">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Some avatars not rendered in contact list </summary>
			<description>Go to main conversation list Tap the pen icon on the lower right to get to the contact list Tap your device's Back button to hide the keyboard that just popped up Some contact avatars do not get rendered at all This affects both picture contacts and initial creation contacts. Scrolling usually fixes the issue or moves it to another contact. It seems that if you dismiss the keyboard (step 3) quickly it increases the likelihood of missing avatars. TS 2.14.5 Nexus 4, stock Android 5.1 Huawei U8800, Android 4.0.4 Debug log: https://gist.github.com/74ba14ab06491edd4749 (On the second try 4 avatars not rendered)</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/PushContactSelectionActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/PushContactSelectionListFragment.java</file>
			<file>res/layout/push_contact_selection_list_item.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/NewConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/GroupCreateActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/636b11abea7a520e1c69c59f69055c5ab112e70f</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="1033">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>group notifications in notification drawer just shows the sender not the group name </summary>
			<description>when i get a group message it always just shows the sender in the notification drawer instead of a combination with the group name. at your daily business you maybe don't want to tap for every update in your group discussions, but you want to answer your private chats. at the moment you can not differentiate between private and group messages at your notification drawer. this is how it looks like at the moment: and something like that would be awesome ;-)</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/MessageNotifier.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/NotificationItem.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/notifications/SingleRecipientNotificationBuilder.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/3b80e3554732865e42406e36f4bf38bef661af5a</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3624">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Crash while inside conversation </summary>
			<description>3ae1c5c https://gist.github.com/0ee0dbe5f17c5551b9cf may contain traces of camera</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/camera/CameraView.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/63515e967e9cde49ab39da1f7c5a6872fcfd496a</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2506">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Crash Browser -- APN Exception </summary>
			<description>java.lang.RuntimeException: An error occured while executing doInBackground()</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/ApnDatabase.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/6c59eb052eaec59fc00db9316fcb93676afba11b</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3397">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>per-recipient ringtone setting dialog does not represent setting state </summary>
			<description>start conversation with A tap A in the top left corner Ringtone > <whatever> notice summary says <whatever> tap Ringtone notice dialog always defaults to nothing selected</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/RecipientPreferenceActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/preferences/AdvancedRingtonePreference.java</file>
			<file>res/xml/recipient_preferences.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/140cbe9f2522ac21b36312bab67a0c73393ed15d</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5651">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Add shortcut to jump to end of conversation </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Feature Request When you are in a conversation and scrolled a bit away from the most recent message (upwards direction) a shortcut to the bottom of the conversation could be displayed near the scroll bar. This would make it easier to return to the most recent messages after reading some old messages. Screenshot (WhatsApp) 👍 7</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/values/dimens.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_fragment.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationFragment.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/aa9d8e4d147dbe70815f078e763e7299b57acdce</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3546">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Upload indicators gone wild </summary>
			<description>Edit: official 2.21 play release on Sony Z1 compact 5.0.2 new group (to be clean) send image 1, wait for completed upload send image 2, notice the indicator shortly popping up on image 1 send image 3, have the 2 circles of eternal life on image one and two</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/MmsSendJob.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationItem.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/SendJob.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ThumbnailView.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/PushMediaSendJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/1bdfb5f3829157eeca54be86a9bee9f4b6fe8d24</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="299">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Implement "Quick Responses" </summary>
			<description>Android has an useful option for rejecting call with SMS. When you receive a call, you can reject it with pre-prepared or custom SMS. However, this SMS is not sent through TextSecure but through default Android application for sending SMS's. Can this be changed?</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/service/QuickResponseService.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/service/MasterSecretIntentService.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/dc60c011a6a15a259783a648255155f5f0042bca</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2498">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Battery usage </summary>
			<description>Since one of the last updates TextSecure uses a lot the battery of my smartphone. Here are the logs: https://gist.github.com/95e27acc2af1b32d7a13</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/MmsSendJob.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/MmsDownloadJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/96896bf8f1bcbc83d1d4a9329ad21287b5efdc30</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2739">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Messages sent to group delivered to private chat after the sender uses a new PreKey </summary>
			<description>Sender's Device: LG G3 running Lolipop, TextSecure 2.6.4 / 2.7.1 (not sure) Receiver's Device: Nexus 5 running Lolipop, TextSecure 2.7.1 Issue details: An existing TextSecure user switched to a new phone and installed TextSecure on it The user sent a message to an existing group member which accepted his new identity then added him to the group. Other group members did not yet approve his new identity. Whenever the user with a new identity sends a message to the group, users who didn't yet accept his new identity receive a "private chat notification" asking them to confirm his unknown identity or cancel. after confirming each "confirm identity" notification, the message which was supposed to be delivered to the group is delivered to the private chat instead of group chat. no idea about future messages, but i believe they would be delivered normally to the group after confirming the identity.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/jobs/PushDecryptJob.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/e32736359ba910eb9bd0b6bd200d3b0866238094</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3396">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>per-recipient vibrate setting dialog does not represent setting state </summary>
			<description>start conversation with A tap A in the top left corner Vibrate > Disable notice summary says disabled tap Vibrate notice dialog always defaults to "Settings default"</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/RecipientPreferenceActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/23b274c472884e54d652ba3ccc3b0b475f295d2b</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2936">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>native system emoji overriding TextSecure-provided ones </summary>
			<description>Hello, the Emoji drawer in TextSecure currently is using the Google "Noto Color Emoji" Emoji set. A lot of Android phones do not have the Google "Noto Color Emoji" Emoji set as their native system Emoji set though. Samsung uses their own Emoji set, LG uses their own Emoji set, HTC uses their own Emoji set and so on... You can see some of those Emoji sets over there: http://emoji.codes/family Unfortunately though, TextSecure does not replace the native system Emojis with the Google "Noto Color Emoji" Emojis, when the native system Emojis are not the Google "Noto Color Emoji" Emojis, like on Samsung, LG and HTC devices for example. So, when Samsung/LG/HTC users tap on one of the Google "Noto Color Emoji" Emojis in the TextSecure Emoji drawer, a Samsung/LG/HTC Emoji appears in the message input box and in the messages themselves, and not the Google "Noto Color Emoji" Emojis the user actually selected. So, could you please replace/overwrite the Emojis in the message input box and in the messages (and everywhere else where it is possible) with the Emojis that are being used in the Emoji drawer? Telegram for Android also has a built-in Emoji drawer and also has built-in Emojis. And Telegram for Android does replace/overwrite the Emojis in the message input box and in the messages (and everywhere else where it is possible) with the Emojis that are being used in the Emoji drawer. So it is possible to do it. Could you please fix this and do it like Telegram for Android is doing it? Regards</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/emoji_drawer_stub.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
			<file>AndroidManifest.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_list_item_view.xml</file>
			<file>build.gradle</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_bubble_outgoing.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/emoji_drawer.xml</file>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_bubble_incoming.xml</file>
			<file>res/values/attrs.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/bf133c65c388f93cd408d0cd9fc0599846f881c2</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="6007">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>After leaving a group I can still change disappearing messages setting </summary>
			<description>I have: searched open and closed issues for duplicates read https://github.com/WhisperSystems/Signal-Android/wiki/Submitting-useful-bug-reports Bug description I am in a group chat with someone and when I leave the group I am still able to change disappearing messages setting. Steps to reproduce become a part of a group chat leave a group choose disappearing messages from menu change a setting Actual result: Group members are sending messages with new setting. Expected result: Disappearing messages settings can be changed only be existing members of a group chat. Device info Device: Multiple Android version: 4.3+ Signal version: 3.25.4</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ComposeText.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/3861084ea212b3d040dbc3d76453ae8da713c3b0</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5297">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Writing at least 1 letter and then going back makes the message line "jump" down/up </summary>
			<description>Open a chat Write "A" Remove "A" The background "Send Signal..." message will go down in the message bar. Trust me, you will see what I mean. Easily reproducable on Moto G (2015)</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/ComposeText.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/5ce4e5a630aab2f9d6e7d03cac74643bcc45c11a</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5295">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Taking a picture with the camera under attachments results in blank message </summary>
			<description>When I try to send a picture taken with "camera" under attachments in Signal nothing is actually sent. Everything is the same as it should, except when I try to send the picture the message is blank. Adding a message to the picture only sends the picture. This only started happening this morning when I installed the latest beta. Open a chat Click attachment icon Click camera Take a picture Accept picture Send the picture Blank message Moto G (2015) Android 6.0.0 Signal is the last beta https://gist.github.com/anonymous/aec4ccbbf8c887ab2b0e https://gist.github.com/anonymous/212ba2b19eba908789a1</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/providers/PersistentBlobProvider.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/a7cbe5e2a2c447b78a699ec4a9660e9ed6a83fbd</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3627">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>can't scroll all the way up in most conversations </summary>
			<description>Both with ts users and sms conversations. Ts 2.22, android 4.1.2</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>res/layout/conversation_activity.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/b75a04eb08931331886cf779bca615b6bc017286</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="3633">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Scrolling inputs emoji </summary>
			<description>When scrolling through Textsecures own emoji it inputs an emoji unless you release outside of the keyboard. Version 2.22.0</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiPopup.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/components/emoji/EmojiPageView.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/0af902b81c9d19a52889c526b48d5e6b9bfaf3d1</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2505">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Crash Browser - NPE </summary>
			<description>java.lang.RuntimeException: Unable to start activity ComponentInfo{org.thoughtcrime.securesms/org.thoughtcrime.securesms.PlayServicesProblemActivity}: java.lang.NullPointerException</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/PlayServicesProblemFragment.java</file>
			<file>res/values/strings.xml</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/95a94eeebf26674f241459a2fecdaed9b555d9f9</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2883">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>forward message to contact for which you have no existing conversation, broken. </summary>
			<description>open some conversation select some text message in that conversation click "Forward message" select a contact for which you don't have an existing conversation action bar updates as expected but conversation view still shows messages from original thread</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationFragment.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/efb4f388a50fec8bca9dcf781c55bdf530bdba82</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="5337">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>3.14 crashes during call </summary>
			<description>When I make a call in Signal with v3.14, the app crashes and the call fails. (Unfortunately etc.) Android 5.1.1, Experia Z3 (Cyanogenmod 12.1) I have tried the following: Reboot Uninstall, re-install 3.14 Same problem. Removing 3.14 and replacing with 3.13.1 fixes the problem. I would give logcat, but this is my DD and I have Signal working again.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>proguard-spongycastle.pro</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/e0f6a92c738763f6ded3fc890625c8d09dc025a9</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2855">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Can't share to TextSecure via the share intent </summary>
			<description>As of 0ff9925 ("move routing logic to all activities"), sharing via an intent doesn't work. To reproduce: Share some text to TextSecure (via some other app's "Share" functionality) TextSecure will show the "Share with" menu with some contacts (and a plus button) Tap a contact (or tap the plus button and select one from the list) The contact's thread will open (or if it was a new contact, a new thread will be created), but the shared text won't be prefilled in the text box. Android 4.4.4 (CM11), commit 0ff9925 .</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationFragment.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ShareActivity.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/ca2c8b961e9b756be6c3478f423a8f77eb102f1c</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2706">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>Video needs to be saved on disc to be playbacked </summary>
			<description>I received a MP4 file from an iOS user (don't know if that has an impact); by trying to playback out of the conversation with vlc i received an error message: can not connect to file, please try to update media db. After saving the file playback was possible on my Nexus 4 running LRX22C version 2.6.4.</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/providers/PartProvider.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/01020c1c09bfe23cda7eabfebc3a026d53551d5a</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
	<bug id="2262">
		<buginformation>
			<summary>hidden conversation when all messages deleted before writing new ones </summary>
			<description>enter existing conversation delete all messages right(at least it sounds similar) write a new one exit conversation --> not in conversation list</description>
		</buginformation>
		<fixedFiles>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/SmsDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/MmsDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationActivity.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/database/ThreadDatabase.java</file>
			<file>src/org/thoughtcrime/securesms/ConversationFragment.java</file>
		</fixedFiles>
		<Commits>
			<commit_url>https://github.com/signalapp/Signal-Android/commit/9ba19df2af48d06780f8defe3ae91bfa5443d30b</commit_url>
		</Commits>
	</bug>
